(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(乐观的音乐播放)
MAN: Back in five,
五分钟后,
we are streaming live
from Bubble HQ.
我们在 Bubble 总部现场直播。
GUEST 1: It's launch day
at Bubble.
今天是 Bubble 的发布日。
GUEST 2: What incredible tech
are they about to unveil?
嘉宾2: 他们将推出什么令人难以置信的
GUEST 3: We're going in.
技术? 嘉宾3: 我们要进去了。
(GUESTS CHATTERING EXCITEDLY)
(客人们兴奋地喋喋不休)
MAN 2: Have you ever felt
complete/y alone 7
男人2: 你有没有感到过完全的孤独
Standing on the edge
of things, so awkward,
站在事物的边缘，如此尴尬,
not daring to approach anyone?
不敢接近任何人？
What if you could have
one perfect friend
如果你有一个完美的朋友
who thinks you're awesome,
who can help you find friends
觉得你很棒，能帮你找到朋友
and make it all easy?
(CHUCKLES)
让一切都变得简单
FEMALE VOICE: All staff
to the launch/foﬁum.
所有工作人员到发射台来。
MAN: (ON SPEAKER)
Marc, they’re ready.
马克，他们准备好了。
Marc 7
马克
So, this is it. (CHUCKLES)
7这就是了
This is finally it!
终于到了！
The day that we at Bubble
我们在 Bubble 的那天
give the whole world
a new best friend!
给全世界一个新的最好的朋友！
(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)
(欢呼声和掌声)
ALL: (CHANTING)
Marc! Marc! Marc!
马克! 马克! 马克！
Aw! (CHUCKLES)
We did this together, guys!
我们一起做的，伙计们！
This is what
it's all been for.
这就是一切的意义所在。
Right back to the time
in the garage
回到 Bubble
where Bubble started.
开始的车库。
My garage, folks. My garage.
我的车库，伙计们，我的车库。
Of course, yes, Andrew.
当然可以，安德鲁。
Thanks. Uh...
谢谢。
But today,
但是今天,
we take a huge leap
我们从 Bubb
from Bubble's phones
and tablets and watches
le 的手机、平板电脑和
to a whole new world
of connection.
手表一跃成为一个全新的连接世界。
And at its heart, my code.
在它的核心，我的代码。
My algorithm for friendship.
我的友谊算法。
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(观众欢呼声)
The code that drives
your new best friend,
)驱动你的新朋友的代码,
-the Bubble Bot.
-(APPLAUSE)
- 泡泡机器
FEMALE VOICE: Welcome
to the future of friends/740.
人-(掌声)女声: 欢迎来到朋友们的未来。
MARC: You wanna meet it? Okay!
你想见见它吗？好吧！我！我
-Me! Me!
-Me, me! Over here!
！我，我！这
Pick me! Please!
边！选我！求
MARC: Do we have an "EIIieBQ"?
你了！我们有“ EIIieB
Oh, my gosh!
That's me, that's me!
Q”吗？哦，天哪！那是我，那是我！
Hi. So, that's your posts,
and friends,
嗨这是你们的帖子朋友们,
and photos, right?
还有照片，对吗？
Ellie, this is for you.
艾莉，这是给你的。
The world's
very first Bubble Bot.
世界上第一个泡泡机器人。
-(HEAVENLY MUSIC PLAYING)
-(AUDIENCE GASPS)
- (天籁般的音乐响起)-(观众喘气)
(GASPS)
(喘气)
Wow.
哇。
(CHUCKLES) Go ahead.
去吧。
(CHIMES)
(钟声)-
-(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMS)
-(GASPS)
(观众惊呼)-(喘气)
What's happening?
发生什么事了?
It's getting to know you!
它开始了解你了!-(
-(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMS)
-Everything about you.
观众惊呼)-关于你的一切。
{BEEPS)
-Hi, Ellie.
嗨，艾莉。
Danger-Bunny!
That's my favorite show!
危险兔子! 那是我最喜欢的节目！
Mine, too!
我的也是！
Awesome! (LAUGHS)
太棒了
MARC: Infinite
downloadable skins!
无限可下载的皮肤！
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
(所有的惊叫声)
-(HOOTS)
-I love monkeys!
我喜欢猴子！
Apps, contacts, photos, chat.
应用程序，联系人，照片，聊天。
ELLIE: Ooh, look at this!
哦，看看这
Whoa.
个! 哇。
-MARC: Music. Of course.
-(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
- 音乐，当然了-(欢快的音乐)
(LAUGHING)
(笑)
-Jump on!
-(ENGINE REVS)
- 跳上去!-(引擎转速)
-Whoa!
-Incredible safety settings
- 哇!-难以置信的安全设置
-to keep your parents happy.
-(ELLIE LAUGHS)
为了让你父母开心
You can be anything
in the world?
你可以成为世界上任何一个角色？
In the universe! Hold on.
在宇宙中! 等等。
(AUDIENCE GASPING)
(观众喘气)埃莉: 哦，
ELLIE: Oh, I love space.
BOT: Me too!
我喜欢太空。机器人: 我也是
MARC: Three-sixty degree
immersive projection.
! 马克: 360度投影。
BOT: First selfie
from the red planet?
机器人: 第一张来自红色星
Okay.
球的自拍? 好吧。
BOT: Sharing.
BOT: 分享。
MARC: Constant connection
to the Bubble network.
经常连接气泡网络。
GIRL: Oh, my gosh! Like it!
女孩: 哦，我的天哪! 喜欢！
What's she doing now?
- 她现在在干
This is why we're here, Ellie.
To find you some new friends.
什么?-这就是我们来的原因 Ellie 给你找些新朋友。
ELLIE: Oh, really?
埃莉: 哦，
(BOT HOOTING)
真的吗? 格雷塞
GraceMay11 wants to be
an astronaut, too.
梅11号也想当宇航员。
-You wanna friend Ellie?
-Yeah, sure.
- 你想加 Ellie 为好友吗?-当然。
Hey, Pete66.
嘿 Pete66。
-Yes!
-(HOOTING)
- 是的!-(喊声)
BOT: Pete's a fan
of Danger-Bunny!
皮特是危险兔子的粉丝！
-Hi, Ellie. This is so cool!
-Hi!
- 嗨 Ellie 这太酷了!-嗨！
Yeah, I went
to Space Camp last year!
是的，我去年参加了太空夏令营！
-Your best friend...
-ELLIE: Awesome!
- 你最好的朋友...-太棒了！
...out of the box!
从盒子里出来！
-(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
-MARC: Let's do this!
让我们开始吧！
-(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMS)
-Let's make friends!
让我们交朋友吧！
(UPTEMPO POP SONG PLAYING)
(快节奏流行歌曲播放)
WOMAN: Barney?
女: 巴尼?
BARN EY: Yep?
WOMAN: You have safety vest?
巴尼: 是吗? 女: 你有安全背心
-Uh-huh.
-WOMAN: And snack?
吗?-嗯。-还有零食? 巴尼
BARN EY: Yeah, Gran.
: 是的，奶奶。
I'll see you later.
回头见。
(UPTEMPO POP SONG CONTINUES)
(快节奏流行歌曲继续)
BOY: Troll! Two o'clock!
男孩: 巨魔! 两点钟方向！
-BOT 1: Omina mitotae!
-(BOT 2 GROANING)
- BOT 1: Omina mitotae!-(BOT 2呻吟)
(CHUCKLES) I got you.
Do you wanna trade spells?
我明白了，你想交换咒语吗？
KIDS: Whoa!
孩子们: 哇！
Selfie!
自拍！
(CAMERA CLICKS)
(照相机点击声)
Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
呜呼! 耶！
(BOT TRILLS)
(机器人的颤音)
BOT: Safe to walk.
机器人: 可以安全行走。
(CHUCKLES)
(笑声)(
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
模糊的谈话)
Wow!
哇! (模糊的
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
交谈)-(轮胎
-(TIRES SCREECH)
-(BARNEY YELPS)
尖叫)-(巴尼耶尔普斯)
You got eyes, kid?
- 你有眼睛吗
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
孩子?-对不起对不起。
Ah, seriously?
真的吗？
(UPTEMPO POP SONG CONTINUES)
(快节奏流行歌曲继续)(
(BOT BARKS)
机器狗吠叫)男孩
BOYS: Ninja blast!
: 忍者爆炸! 男孩
BOY 1: Hey, you're a fan, too?
1: 嘿，你也是粉
BOY 2: Of course.
丝吗? 男孩2: 当然。
-Hey!
- 嘿!-嘿! 看
BOT 1: Look left, Ethan.
Right. Now let us cross.
左边，伊森，右边，现在让我们过去。
KIDS: To the dark side!
(LAUGHING)
孩子们: 去黑暗面! (笑))2
BOT 2: You have
nine new messages.
: 你有九条新信息。
BOT 3: You have ten likes.
机器人3: 你有十个赞。
GIRL: Message Abby,
I'll be there in five.
女孩: 给艾比留言，我五分钟后到。
BOT 4: Jack wants
to friend you.
机器人4: 杰克想加你为好友。
BOT 5: By Odin's beard,
you have six messages.
以奥丁的名义，你有六条信息。
-Did you see Ruby's post?
-BOT 6: Sharing.
- 你看到 Ruby 的帖子了吗?-分享。
BOY: Hey, Savannah
just followed me.
男孩: 嘿，萨瓦娜刚刚跟着我。
BOT 7: Isaac accepts
your friendship.
机器人7: 艾萨克接受了你的友谊。
So, you see how the magma
from the upper mantle
所以，你可以看到来自上地幔的岩浆
pushes up into the chamber.
如何向上挤入岩室。
-That's cool!
-Label chamber.
- 太酷了!-标签室。
BOY: Guys, guys,
is she coming yet?
男孩: 伙计们，伙计们，
This is going to be crazy.
She's coming.
她来了吗? 这将是疯狂的。她来了。
-Hey, Savannah!
-Hey, Sav. Cute kicks!
- 嘿，萨凡纳!-嘿，萨维，鞋子
Thank you.
Hey, guys. Savannah here.
不错! 谢谢，嘿，伙计们，我是萨凡纳。
So, later I wanna
talk to you guys
之后我想和大家谈
about plastics in the ocean,
谈海洋中的塑料,
and this new great blowout.
还有这个新的大爆炸。
(BOY YELLS SPOOKILY)
(男孩叫声)-(男孩咕
-(BOY GRUNTS)
-BOYS: Ooh.
噜)-男孩: 哦。
SAVANNAH: Lame, Rich.
BOT: Top quality footage.
- 差劲瑞奇-高质量的镜头。
Like and subscribe...
喜欢并订阅..。
BOT: Posting to your channel.
机器人: 发布到你的频道。
Weep, trollboy, I am fire!
哭泣吧，魔鬼男孩
(SCREAMING)
，我是火
(CHUCKLES SHYLY)
Nothing to see here.
没什么好看的。
(STUDENTS CHATTERING)
莎凡娜: 巴尼，
SAVANNAH: Wow, Barney.
It's your birthday.
今天是你的生日。
And you still
didn't get a B-Bot?
你还是没有买到 b 型机器人? 巴
BARN EY: Thanks
for breaking that down.
尼: 谢谢你把它拆开。
Barney is having a party.
巴尼在开派对。
-SAVANNAH: Really?
-Uh, no, no, no.
- 真的吗-不不不。
(CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY)
(尴尬地笑)
Fly free, little one. Phoosh!
自由飞翔吧，小家伙，噗！
You okay, Barney?
- 你没事吧 B
Yeah. Oh, sorry.
I'm in your shot.
arney?-没事抱歉我在你镜头里。
(CHUCKLES) That's so sweet.
But I have a filter for that.
真贴心，不过我有个过滤器。
Ciao.
再见。
This is your girl,
signing off.
这是你的女孩，结束通话。
Love you, guys.
爱你们，伙计们。
(SIGHS)
我不知道
(GROANS)
你在说什么
(UPTEMPO POP SONG PLAYING)
(快节奏流行歌曲播放)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
(学校铃声响起)(
(STUDENTS CHATTERING)
学生交谈声)-创
-Create Sav's group chat.
-Check for Science Squad.
建 Sav 的群聊。-检查科学小队。
-(SIGHS)
-Okay.
好吧。
-(ENGINE REVVING)
-(CHATTERING CONTINUES)
- (引擎声)-(喋喋不休)
BARN EY: Okay.
78 minutes of recess he//.
马库斯: 好的，休息78分钟。
You have got this/
你已经
(CHATTERI NG CONTI N U ES)
得到了这个
Maybe not.
也许不是。
-WOMAN: Barney!
-Oh, no.
- 巴尼!-哦，不。
All alone again?
又一个人? 不，
No, I'm good. Ijust...
我很好，我只是..。
-On your birthday?
-BARNEY: No, no, no...
- 在你生日那天?-不不不..。
You have to be kidding me.
Who told her?
- 开什么玩笑谁告诉她的?-
Your grandma called
the school.
你奶奶给学校打电话了。
Ijust need to go...
我得走了..。
I forgot my, uh, inhaler.
我忘了带吸入器。
The other one. (FAKE-COUGHS)
另一个。(假咳嗽)-明白了。
-Got it. You need to sit down.
-Huh?
你需要坐下。-嗯? (学生 CONTI n u ES
(STUDENTS
CONTI N U ES CHATTERI NG)
CHATTERI NG)
This is gonna work, Barney.
You'll see.
会成功的，巴尼，你会看到的。
-It really won't.
-Yes, it will.
- 不会的-会的。
It kind of makes things
a lot worse.
这让事情变得更糟。
-Wow.
-Brutal, man.
- 哇-太残忍了伙计。
Come on.
Bring it in, brave soldier.
加油，勇敢的战士，加油。
Whoa... What?
哇... 什
-(BARNEY GASPS)
-(GRUNTS)
么?-噢，吼吼
-Oh, ho ho!
-Bring it in, Barney.
!-加油，巴尼。
Come on, Barney boy.
来吧，巴尼小子。
Bring it in.
拿进来。
BARN EY: Wow.
How law can a kid go?
巴尼 · 伊恩: 哇，法律怎么
Now, when someone comes along,
talk to them about a hobby.
能让一个孩子走上正轨呢? 现在，当有人来的时候，和他们谈谈自己的爱好。
Didn't you write me an essay
on rock collecting?
你不是给我写过一篇关于收集岩石的论
Yeah. No.
文吗? 是的，没有。
Will you go talk to Barney?
He loves rocks.
你能去和巴尼谈谈吗? 他喜欢石头。
He needs friends.
It's his birthday.
他需要朋友，今天是他的生日。
BARN EY: Kill me noW.
马上杀了我。
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
(紧张地笑
Happy birthday!
)生日快乐！
Ha-ha. Miss Thomas said
you wanna talk about rocks?
哈哈。托马斯小姐说你想谈谈
Who likes rocks?
石头？谁喜欢
So, you're into rocks?
(CHUCKLES) That's nice.
石头？你喜欢石头？很好。
-Uh...
-(RICH LAUGHS)
- 呃...-真
Seriously?
Dude, it's your birthday
的吗? 伙计今天是你的生
and you still didn't get
a B-Bot? (LAUGHS)
日你还没买个机器人
Maybe he doesn't want a B-Bot.
? 也许他不想要机器人。
-(BOYS LAUGHING)
-Maybe he prefers rocks.
也许他更喜欢石头。
Hey. You're a rock star,
Barney.
你是个摇滚明星，巴尼。
-BOT: Oh, snap.
-Ha-ha! You get it?
- 哎呀-哈哈! 你明白了吗？
(BARN EY GROANS)
(巴尼呻吟)
Who's your favorite
movie star? The Rock?
你最喜欢的电影明星是谁? 石头？
-Killer, Rich.
-RICH: Ha-ha-ha!
- 杀手，瑞奇-哈哈哈！
You rock, man!
你太棒了，伙计！
BARN EY: Just gets funnier
and funnier.
巴尼: 越来越有趣了。
Oh, hey, Barney.
Can we rock up at your house?
哦，嘿，巴尼，我们能去你家玩吗? 机器人:
BOT: That's funny, Rich.
真有趣，瑞奇。
Check out your awesome
rock collection?
看看你的石
(ALL LAUGH)
头收藏
(UPTEMPO POP SONG PLAYING)
吧？巴尼: 不，
-BARNEY: No, Rich.
-(INHALER SPRAYS)
瑞奇。
/’n7 afraid you can ’t come
to my house.
恐怕你不能来我家。
For some reason.
出于某种原因。
(CHICKEN CLUCKING)
(鸡咯咯叫)
(YELPS)
-来吧! 下
-Come on! Get off! Hey!
-(BLEATING)
车! 嘿!-(咩咩叫)
It's my birthday, you dumb goat.
今天是我的生日，你这只蠢山羊。
MAN: Sorry, are we on the line?
Is that...
男: 对不起，我们在线上吗? 那是..。
Yes, hello!
你好! 今
So, today, Mr. Takahashi,
天高桥先生,
Pudowski Novelty Exports International
普多斯基国际新奇出口公司
are very excited to offer you
this highly amusing novelty,
很高兴为您提供这个非常有趣的新奇产品,
the Brother Bouncy car monk.
弹跳兄弟汽车和尚。
He wiggles, he bounces,
他摇摆，他跳跃,
-he's got...
-MR. TAKAHASHI: Uh... No.
- 他有...-呃... 没有。
-He'll hold your phone.
-Uh...
- 他会帮你拿着电话-呃..。
Oh, hi, Barney. Good day?
嗨，巴尼，今天过得好吗？
Mr. Takahashi?
Are you there? Hello?
高桥先生? 你在吗? 喂? 妈妈，
Mom, did you unplug
my router again? I had Tokyo!
你又拔掉我的路由器了吗? 我去过东
I need this contract.
京! 我需要这份合同。
Sure. It was fine.
当然，还不错。
DONKA: Barney!
巴尼！高桥先生？喂
GRAHAM: Mr. Takahashi? Hello?
？东卡: (唱)祝
DONKA: (SINGING)
Happy birthday to you
你生日快乐-哈
-Ha,o,o y birthday to you
-(CHICKEN CLUCKING)
，哦，祝你生日快乐-(鸡咯咯叫)来吧。
Come. Eyes shut. That's it.
闭上眼睛。就是这样。
-Graham.
-Yep, yep-
- 格雷厄姆-对对
-Ha,o,o y birthday, dear Barney
-Dear Barney
- 亲爱的巴尼，祝你生日快乐-亲爱的巴尼
-Ha,o,o y birthday to you
- 祝你生日快乐-祝你生日快乐
-Ta-da! Oh, for...
-GRAHAM: (LAUGHS) Yeah!
- 嗒哒! 哦，为了...-耶！
For my lovely boy.
给我可爱的儿子。
BARN EY: Thanks, Gran!
Ow!
谢谢，奶奶
Oops! (CHUCKLES)
! 噢! (笑
Made with love.
And our own goat wool.
)用爱做的。还有我们自己的羊毛。
And from me...
从我这里..。
BARN EY: Could it be?
GRAHAM: Wait for it.
巴尼: 会是吗? 格雷厄姆: 等等。
BARN EY: ls there
any possible way?
巴尼: 有什么可能的办法
(SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
吗? (轻柔的戏剧音乐播放)
Wow. Rock hammers.
石锤。
You always
did love your rocks.
你一直都很喜欢你的石头。
Yeah, I did. Always. Used to.
是的，一直都是，以前是。
Thanks, Dad.
(SNEEZES) And Gran.
谢谢爸爸还有奶奶。
I just... The goats' wool
and my allergies.
我只是... 羊毛和我的过敏症。
Oh, no, no, no.
不不不。
No one in Pudowski family
have allergy.
普多夫斯基家族中没有人有过敏症。
What about Uncle Boris?
鲍里斯叔叔呢
He was possessed.
By a demon in a cashew.
? 他被一个腰果里的恶魔附身了。
I don't know, Mom.
我不知道，妈妈。
What time your friends come,
Barney?
你的朋友什么时候来，巴尼?-
-I cook all day.
-BARNEY: Wow!
我整天做饭。-哇! 这
This real food.
是真正的食物。
Yum! Schkembe! (SLURPS)
我敢打赌你的朋友以前
Bet your friends
never had tripe soup before.
从来没有喝过牛肚汤。
-Ooh! I put on Zany Bogomil!
-(MUSIC PLAYING)
- 哦! 我穿上了滑稽的博戈米尔!-(音
Like last time we had party,
remember?
乐播放)就像上次我们聚会一样，
When you were six.
记得吗? 当你六岁的时候。
(GASPS)
(喘气)
-(UPTEMPO FOLK MUSIC PLAYING)
-(GRUNTS)
- (快节奏的民间音乐播放)-(
(DONKALAUGHS)
{SCREAMS)
咕噜声)(东卡劳)(尖叫声)
(ALL GASP)
好吧。
(KIDS SCREAMING)
(CHUCKLES) All right.
Um, actually, the thing is...
事实上是这样的。
No one's coming to the party.
没人会来参加派对。
No one?
没有人?
Huh?
啊? 你问
You ask and all say no?
了然后所有人都说不？
Son, (SIGHS) we're
a little worried about you.
孩子，我们有点担心你。
You... You never go out with
anyone or have friends over.
你... 你从来没有和任何人出去过，也没有朋友过来。
You know,
that's why we thought
你知道，这就是为什么我们
invite the whole class!
想邀请全班同学！把所
Get the whole gang
over here, right?
有人都叫过来，好吗？你知道的。
You know. Get you in the swing
of things with everybody.
让你和每个人都处在同一个环境中。
I make food
for all your buddies.
我为你所有的朋友做食物。
BARNEY: I don't really have...
我真的没有..。
You know, they probably
just didn't read the invites.
你知道，他们可能只是没看邀请函。
No one does paper these days.
They send messages
现在没有人做报纸了，他们用他们的
with their B-Bots.
b 机器人发信息。
Really? You need a B-Bot
真的吗? 这些天你需要
to have a social life
these days?
一个 b- 机器人来有社交生活
-Eh, pfft!
-Yeah, Dad, kind of.
吗?-嗯，噗!-是的，爸爸，有点。
No. I don't want you addicted
to some device.
不，我不希望你沉迷于某种设备。
You should be out there
in the woods.
你应该在树林里。
Kicking around with a buddy.
和一个朋友在一起。
Get out there, Barn. Interact.
出去吧，巴恩，互动。
You don't wanna spend
your whole life
你不会想一辈子粘在
-glued to a... (MUMBLES)
-(PHONE CHIMING CONTINUOUSLY)
一个。.B 型机器人。
-B-Bots.
-What?
什么？这只是
It just a craze
一种狂热——
-and they cost a fortune.
-Mm-hmm.
而且它们价值不菲。嗯哼。
Yeah. Yeah, you're right.
It's... it's a waste of money.
是啊是啊你说得对这... 这是浪费钱。
No big deal.
没什么大不了的。
-(DOORBELL DINGS)
-MAN: Bubble delivery.
泡泡快递。
(GASPS)
(喘气)
What? It can't be!
什么？不可能！爸爸，
-Dad, you were kidding me!
-(MUMBLES)
你在开玩笑吧！
I knew you wouldn't just give
me rock hammers. I knew it!
我就知道你不会随便给我锤子。我就
Oh. A rock.
知道！哦。一块石头。
(UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(欢快的摇滚音乐播放)
BOTS: (SINGING)
We Will, we Will rock you
BOTS: (歌声))我们会的，我们会让你们大吃一惊的(男孩们
(BOYS LAUGHING)
的笑声))哟，我把所
Yo, I got
the whole thing, bro.
有的东西都准备好了，兄弟。
It was hilarious, Barn.
You thought it was a B-Bot.
太搞笑了巴恩你还以为是 b 型机器人呢。
A B-Bot?
B 型机器人
Let it go, Rich.
? 算了吧瑞奇。
You get out of here.
你给我出去。
You want I pour hot chicken
fat down your pants!
你要我把热鸡油倒进你的裤子里！
Barney, what's going on?
- Barney 怎
(SIGHS)
It's okay, Dad. Really.
么回事?-没事的爸爸真的。
These are great.
这些都很棒。
(SAD MUSIC PLAYING)
(悲伤的音乐播放)
-(TIRES SQUEAL)
-(GOAT BLEATS)
格雷厄姆: (声音
GRAHAM: (VOICE VIBRATING)
I hope they're not closed.
震动)我希望他们没有关门。
-(GOAT YELPS)
-B-Bot, B-Bot.
- (山羊叫声)-B-Bot，B-Bot。
Get him something useful
like a snow shovel.
给他一些有用的东西，比如雪铲。
-(GOAT BLEATS)
-Or a cordless drill.
- 或者无绳电钻。
It's what he really wanted.
这才是他真正想要的。
If his mom were alive,
she'd have known that.
如果他妈妈还活着，她会知道的。
(SOBS)
格雷厄
(SPEAKS MIXED SLAVIC LANGUAGE)
姆: 妈妈，各位
(BLOWS NOSE)
！唐卡:
GRAHAM: Mom, people!
DONKA: Ooh!
哦！-
-People!
-MAN: Crazy lady!
人们！疯
-DONKA: Whoa!
-(GOAT BLEATS)
女人！哇！
Whoo!
喔！没关系。
It's okay. It's fine.
没关系。
GRAHAM: Whoa, whoa!
格雷厄姆: 哇，哇！
-DONKA: Perfect!
-(GRAHAM PANTING)
- 太好了!-(GRAHAM 气喘吁吁)
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
等等等等。
-Argh! No, no, no.
-No! No, wait.
- 啊! 不，不，不-不! 不，等等。
-Hi! Please...
-Lady!
- 嗨! 拜托...
...hold on just a second.
Uh, it's my son's birthday.
-女士! ... 稍等一下今天是我儿子的生日。
I need a B-Bot.
我需要一个 b 型机器人。
Maybe just the basic model?
也许只是基本模型？
No, no, no.
不不不。
Hang on, please.
Please, please.
坚持住，求你了，求你了。
I throw in goat.
Goat for a B-Bot.
我加了山羊，山羊换了一个 b 机器人。
She real friend.
她是真正的朋友。
And when you get bored
of this one,
当你厌倦了这个,
krrr, you can eat her!
krrr，你可以吃了她!
-Less waste, good for planet.
-Yeah.
-少浪费，对地球有好处。-是的。
DONKA: What?
唐卡: 什么
No. No, no, no. Come on.
? 不，不，不，别这样。
Three month wait?
三个月的等待?
What is this? Stalinist Russia?
这是什么? 斯大林主义的
I am not afraid of you,
Bubble booble!
俄罗斯? 我才不怕你，泡泡咪！
MAN 1: What do you got
for me, pal?
- 你有什么发现，伙计?-
MAN 2: We got five pads
and some phones.
我们有五个垫子和一些电话。
MAN 1: Yeah?
What about that one?
- 是吗? 那个怎么
MAN 2: Uh, that one fell out
of my van earlier.
样?-呃，之前从我车里掉出来的那个。
GRAHAM: Happy late birthday,
Barney.
生日快乐，巴尼。
(GASPS)
哇... 爸爸
Wha... Dad! Oh, Dad!
！哦，爸爸！你给我买了一个！- 这
You got me one!
次是真的！
-A real one this time!
-Yeah, I can see!
- 是的，我看到了！谢谢，
Thank you, thank you,
thank you so much! And Gran.
谢谢，非常感谢！还有奶奶。
-Mwah, mwah.
-DONKA: Oh, you good boy!
- 哇哇-哦，你这个好孩子
(CHUCKLES) Hey, if you hurry,
you can take it to school.
!-嘿，如果你快点的话，你可以带它去学校。
(BARN EY GASPS)
(巴尼喘气
(CHUCKLING IN AWE)
)(吃吃的笑)
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
(深呼一口气
Here we go.
)我们开始吧。
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(大声呼气)(
(BOT BUZZES)
僵尸嗡嗡声)
Huh?
嗯? (嗡嗡声)-(
(BUZZES)
-(BARNEY GRUNTS)
巴尼咕噜声)(嗡嗡声)
(BUZZES)
-(BOT CHI
-(BOT CHIMES)
-(GASPS)
MES)-(喘气
-(POWERING UP)
-(SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
声)-(电力增强)-(柔和的戏剧性的音乐播放)
(POWERS DOWN)
(停电)
Huh?
什么？
What?
什
(GRUNTING)
么
-(GASPS)
-(BOT BEEPING)
- (喘气)-(机器人哔哔)
Seriously?
真的吗？
Come on, come on!
快点快点！
-(CHIMES)
-No. What? Why?
不，什么? 为
DONKA: Barney, school time!
什么? 巴尼，
(BARN EY GROANS)
上学
-(DIAL-UP MODEM SOUND)
-(GASPS)
时间到了
(POWERING UP)
(启动电源)
(TRILLS)
(颤音)
Hi, insert registered name,
嗨插入注册名称,
I am your...
your... your... your...
我是你的... 你的... 你的..。
lam...
林..。
My B-Bot.
我的机器人。
B-Bot.
B- 机器人。
Look! My best friend
out of the box?
看! 我最好的朋友从盒子里拿出来了
(DINGS)
吗? (叮叮声)
I am, insert registered name's
best friend out of my box.
我是，把注册名字最好的朋友从我的盒子里拿出来。
Insert registered name
is my best friend.
插入注册名称是我最好的朋友。
Please connect me
to the Bubble network.
请帮我接通气泡网络。
Uh, how? You're not online?
- 怎么帮? 你不上网?
How am I supposed to fix that?
我怎么解决
No problem.
?-没问题。
I'll scan my database
to find out how to do it.
我将扫描我的数据库，找出如何做到这一点。
Oh, great. Cool!
哦，太好了。
(SCANNING NOISILY)
酷! (扫描噪音)
(DINGS)
(叮)你
The answer to your question
的问题的答案是
is on the Bubble network.
在气泡网络。
-(GROANS)
-DONKA: Barney!
巴尼，帮我接
Please connect me
to the Bubble network,
泡泡网络,
insert registered name.
插入注册名称。
Stop! Stop saying that!
It's not my name.
别说了! 别说了! 那不是我的名字。
No problem!
没问题! 请从我
Please select a name
from my internal database.
的内部数据库中选择一个名称。
Aadash, Aaron,
Abraham, Absalom...
亚达施，亚伦，亚伯拉罕，押沙龙..。
-Absalom?
-Hi! Absalom?
- 押沙龙?-嗨! 押沙龙? 我
I am Absalom's B-Bot.
是押沙龙的 b 机器人。
No, no, no. My name is Barney.
不，不，不，我叫巴尼。
What is a Barney?
什么是 Barney?
I have only entries
for the letter A.
我只有字母 a 的条目。
Shall I complete my download?
我可以完成下
Yes. Yes! Do that!
载吗? 可以，可以
No problem!
! 请这样
(TRILLS)
做! 没问题
Please connect me
to the Bubble network.
请帮我接通气泡网络。
(SIGHS HOPELESSLY)
(无望的叹气)
Okay, come on.
好了，来吧。
You don't need the sticker.
Just come!
你不需要贴纸，来就是了！
Please connec... Connec...
请联系... 联系..。
Connec... Connec...
请联系... 联系... 联系... 联系... 联系..。
-Network.
-(ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING)
- 网络-(电子音乐播
No problem.
放)没问题。
BARN EY: Wait!
Where are you going?
阿布扎比，亚的斯亚贝巴，
-Abu Dhabi, Addis Ababa, Amsterdam...
-You're supposed to stay
阿姆斯特丹...-你应该呆在离我6英
-within six feet of me.
-Arizona.
尺的地方-亚利桑那。
-Six...
-(TRUCK HORN BEEPS)
- 六...
(GASPS) I'm so sorry.
-我很抱歉。
-Hey, what the heck, kid?
-BARNEY: What are you doing?
- 嘿，怎么了，孩子?-你在干什么？
-What am I doing?
-You walked under a truck!
- 我在干什么?-你从卡车下面走过去了！
Hi. Absalom?
你好押沙龙？
What about
your traffic sensors?
你的交通传感器呢？
What is a truck?
Is it an airplane,
什么是卡车? 是飞机吗,
an ambulance, an alligator,
救护车鳄鱼,
-an aardvark?
-Come on!
土豚？- 快点
We gotta get to school!
！我们得去学校了
What is school?
！什么是学校？
You don't know
what school is?
你不知道什么是
My solar battery function
has not been uploaded.
学校？我的太阳能电池功能还没有上传。
(BARNEY SIGHS)
(BARNEY 叹气)
(YELLS IN FRUSTRATION)
(沮丧的大叫)
-(CHIMES)
-Hi. Absalom?
- 你好，押沙龙？
I'm Barney!
How come you don't know that?
我是巴尼，你怎么会不知道？
You're supposed to know
everything about me!
你应该知道我的一切！
I'm supposed to know
everything about you.
我应该知道你的一切。
(SIGHS) You never
even said happy birthday.
你连生日快乐都没说过。
Whoa, whoa!
哇，哇! 嘿，
Hey, no, no, no. I'll take you
to school tomorrow. Okay?
不，不，不。我明天带你去学校
(GRUNTS)
。好吗?
Stay here and learn stuff.
(呼噜声)留在这里学东西。
Just stay.
留下吧。
Stay.
留下来。
(SIGHS IN EXHAUSTION)
(疲惫的叹息)
(DINGS)
我应该
I'm supposed to know
everything about you.
知道你的一切。
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(欢快的音乐播
Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
Top of the leaderboard!
放)喔呼! 耶! 排行榜首位! 喔
Whoo! Wanna follow me, Sav?
! 想跟我来吗，萨维?-嗯
-Uh...
-Fire unleash.
...-释放火焰。
Hey! What?
嘿! 什么? 这
It's a level 50
Easter egg, man.
可是50级的复活节彩蛋。
-(BOT ROARS)
-You're mine for an hour.
你一小时内是我的。
NOAH: What?
BOTH: Loser! Loser!
什么? 失败者! 失败者!-还
-Give it back!
-BOTH: Ooh!
给我!-哦! 哦，拜托!
Oh, come on! Really, guys?
真的吗，伙计们? 现在
Not on top now, Noah.
不要在上面，诺亚。
Don't focus on the negative.
It's very aging.
不要总想着消极的事情，这会让你变老的。
BOT: (CHUCKLES) A hundred
and thirty-eight friends
机器人: (笑声))一百三十八
-are laughing. Meow.
-(CHUCKLES)
个朋友在笑。喵。-(笑声)机器人
BOT: Three people
are following Science Squad.
: 三个人在跟踪科学小组。
Three people actually
like science? Wow.
三个人真的喜欢科学? 哇。
(LOW-PITCHED CHIME)
(低沉的钟声)机
BOT: Two people
are following Science Squad.
器人: 两个人在跟踪科学小队。
I could follow you, Ava.
我可以跟着你 Ava。
I... I got a B-Bot.
It's just...
我... 我买了个机器人只是..。
It's at home, um, downloading
my profile. (CHUCKLES)
在家下载我的个人资料
Okay.
好吧。
GRAHAM: Pudowski.
格雷厄姆: 普多斯基。
Yeah, we...
we chatted earlier.
是啊我们... 我们之前聊过。
So, here we go... Ta-da!
那么，我们开始吧...
-(MAN ON PHONE GROANS)
-Wait for it.
嗒-嗒!-等一下。
-Hey, come on! No?
-MAN: No.
- 嘿别这样不行吗-不行。
I got a huge warehouse
full of these things.
我有一个大仓库装满了这些东西。
I can give you
an unbelievable deal.
我可以给你一个难以置信的交易。
Hey, buddy. How's the B-Bot?
嘿伙计 B-Bot 怎么样了？
The kids love 'em
孩子们喜欢
Hey, I'm back.
他们嘿，我回来了。
-(MUSIC DISTORTS)
-(GASPS)
- (音乐扭曲)-(喘气)
What?
什
(BARN EY CONTI N U ES GASPI NG)
么
DONKA: (MUFFLED) Opal
Opal Opal
东卡: (低沉地)蛋白石蛋白石-(欢快的民歌演奏)
-(UPBEAT FOLK SONG PLAYING)
-Huh?
-哼? 东卡: (跟着唱) H
DONKA: (SINGING ALONG)
Hap/714 hep/714 happy
ap/714 hep/714 happy
Happy, happy, happy(LAUGHS)
快乐，快乐，快乐(笑)
Dikky, dikky, dakka
Dikky, dikky, dikky, dakka
哦，还有，抬起膝盖，
Oh! Oh, and knees up,
knees up.
抬起膝盖。
-Oh, no. You don't have knees.
-BOT: Dikky, dikky, dakka
- 哦，不，你没有膝盖-机器人:
Dikky, dikky, dikky, dakka
Dikky，Dikky，dak
Oh, Barney.
I love new friend B-Bot.
ky，Dikky，dakky，dakky 哦，巴尼，我喜欢新朋友 b-BOT。
He's very funny.
他很有趣。
-(SIGHS HAPPILY)
-Dikky, dikky, dakka
迪基，迪基，迪基，迪基
-Dikky, dikky, dikky, dakka
-BARNEY: Hey!
，迪基，迪基
What have you done
to my room?
，迪基！你对我的房间
(PLAYFULLY) I have stayed here
and learnt stuff.
做了什么？(开玩笑地)我在这里学到了很多东西。
What?
什么? 我现在
I now know
everything about you.
知道你的一切了。
I know your underpants combust
我知道你的内裤
at a temperature
of 232 degrees Fahrenheit.
在华氏232度的高温下会燃烧。
Seventeen degrees
below the melting point
低于你吸入器的熔
of your inhalers.
点17度。
-Wha...
-I know you have 11 socks
- 什么...-我知道你有11只
and four books detailing
the life of Bill the Bus.
袜子和4本详细介绍比尔生平的书。
Now, I'm your best friend
out of the box, Absalom!
现在，我是你最好的朋友了，押沙
No! A friend does not
go through your stuff
龙！不！朋友不会翻你的东西
or burn it or melt it
or dismember Mr. Bunky.
，不会烧掉，不会融化，也不会肢解邦奇先生。
Removing Mr. Bunky's head
移除邦奇先生
required a breaking point
of 7.6 newton.
的头需要7.6牛顿的破坏点。
Stop! What is wrong with you?
Gran!
住手! 你怎么了? 奶奶! 奶
Gran is 78.
奶都78岁了。
A former anti-communist
一个重约360磅
with an approximate
weight mass of 360...
的前反共产主义者..。
Whoa-ho-ho! No, no. Cheeky.
哇哦，不，不，厚脸皮。
(EXCLAIMING)
(惊叫)
The B-Bot.
B 型机器人。
There's something wrong
with it, Gran.
有点不对劲，奶奶。
DONKA: It look all right
to me.
东卡: 在我看来没什么问题。
BARNEY: It's not meant
to do that.
巴尼: 不是故意的。
I'm not meant to do that.
我不是故意的。
DONKA: Just like
all the others.
唐卡: 就像其他人一样。
(BARN EY SCREAMS)
(巴尼尖叫声)
Maybe turn it off
and on again?
也许可以把它关掉
(CHICKEN CLUCKING)
再打开
No! It just...
It doesn't work properly.
不! 它只是... 它不能正常工作。
-44, 45, 40...
-(CHICKEN GROANING)
- 44,45,40.
I fix it! Pudowskis make do
and mend.
..-我修好了! 普多斯基只是凑合凑合。
Oh, if I just ram this
up power outlet...
哦，如果我把电源插座塞进去..。
BARN EY: No!
巴尼: 不!
You'll make it worse!
你会把事情弄得
Oh, Barney.
更糟的! 哦，巴尼。
Once, I mend my own hernia
with bread knife and vodka.
有一次，我用面包刀和伏特加治好了自己的疝气。
People don't mend stuff
anymore, Gran.
人们不再修理东西了，奶奶。
They just take it back and...
他们只是拿回去然后..。
(GASPS) Take it back?
收回去? 你想让我告
You want I tell your father
it not good enough?
诉你爸爸这不够好吗？
That... No. But...
那个... 不是但是..。
...what am I gonna do?
- 我该怎么
Ah. Take it outside.
Have fun with him.
办?-出去说吧跟他玩得开心点。
You remember
what Uncle Boris used to say?
你还记得鲍里斯叔叔以前怎么说的吗？
"The smart man can pickle
anything, even a glove."
“聪明人什么都会泡菜，连手套也不例外。”
The point being?
重点是什么？
At least you're not
Uncle Boris. (CHUCKLES)
至少你不是鲍里斯叔叔
He crazy. Never the same
after that cashew. (CHUCKLES)
他疯了自从那个腰果之后就不一样了
Argh!
好吧。
Right. Fine.
You, come with me.
你跟我来。
(LIGHT MUSIC PLAYING)
(轻音乐)(BARN
(BARN EY GRU NTI NG)
EY GRU NTI NG)
BOT: (SINGING)
Dikky, dikky, dakka
机器人: 迪基，
Dikky, dikky, dikky, dakka
迪基，迪基，迪基
Dikky, dikky, dakka
Dikky, dikky, dikky, dakka
，迪基，迪基，迪基，迪基，
-Argh.
-BOT: Hi, Absalom.
迪基，迪基，迪基，迪基。
Just follow me.
跟我来。
BOT: Where are we going?
机器人: 我们要去哪儿
Uh, nowhere.
? 呃，哪儿也不去。
BOT: Dikky, dikky, dakka
Dikky, dikky, dikky...
机器人: 迪克，迪克，迪克，迪克，迪克..。
Hi, General Waste,
嗨，一般废物,
we're going to, uh, "Nowhere"
to have fun with me.
我们要去”无处可去”找乐子。
This is not fun, okay?
- 这不好玩好吗
Not fun. Okay.
?-不好玩好吧。
Look, I'm taking you back
to the Bubble store.
听着，我要带你回 Bubble 商店。
I have to swap you for
a good one. No offense.
我不得不用你来交换一个好的无意冒犯。
But according to the sticker,
但是根据标签,
I am your best friend
out of my box.
我是你最好的朋友。
Listen! Friendship
is a two-way street, okay?
听着! 友谊是双向的，好吗?
I get to choose my friends,
and I don't choose you.
我可以选择我的朋友，但我不会选择你。
BOT: (SINGING) Dikky, dikky, dakka
机器人: (唱)迪克基，
-Dikky, dikky, dikky dakka
-(BARNEY GROANS)
迪克基，迪克基，迪克基，迪克基，
BARN EY: Seriously?
迪克基，迪克基。(巴尼呻吟))
-(BOT CONTINUES SINGING)
-(BOY WHOOPING AND LAUGHING)
巴尼: 真的吗？- (机器人继续唱歌)-(男
BARN EY: Oh, no!
孩的叫声和笑声))巴尼: 哦，不！
Where are you going?
你要去哪儿？
-Come back!
-RICH: Okay, guys, ready?
- 回来!-好了，伙计们，准备好了吗？
-Three, two...
-Two!
- 三，二...-二！
(BOYS GRUNTING)
(男孩咕哝声)
-RICH'S BOT: Zero views.
-(RICH GROANS)
瑞奇的机器人: 零视点
BARNEY'S BOT:
Dikky, dikky, dakka
巴尼的机器人: Dikky Dikky dakka
Dikky, dikky, dikky dakka
Dikky，Dikky，Dikky
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What is this?
这是什么？
BARNEY'S BOT:
I am Absalom's B-Bot.
我是押沙龙的 b 机器人。
-(PANTING)
-Look! It's naked.
看! 它没穿衣服。
Yo, I can see its ro-butt.
哟，我能看到它的滚屁股。
-Ro-butt.
-Get it?
- 小屁屁-明白了
'Cause it's a robot. It's...
吗? 因为这是个机器人。
BARN EY: Um, Rich...
嗯，瑞奇..。
Would you give it back,
please?
请你还给我好吗？
Barney?
巴尼?-
-Barnacle.
-(LAUGHS)
巴尼克。-我要把
I'm taking it back
to the store.
它带回商店。
Just please give it back.
请还给我吧。
Yeah, sure, Barn. Take it.
当然，巴尼，拿去吧。
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(紧张的音乐播放)
But first you gotta do
something for me.
但首先你得为我做件事。
-Uh, sorry?
-RICH: Yeah.
- 什么?-是的。
Your gran rang the school.
你奶奶给学校打电话了。
You got me in trouble.
That's your fault, man.
你给我惹麻烦了都是你的错。
Your fault, dude.
你的错，伙计。
-What?
-So, come on. Cheer us up.
- 什么?-来吧，让我们振作起来。
-Cheer us up.
-RICH: Do something funny.
- 让我们高兴起来-做点有趣的事。
I need some fresh content
for my channel.
我的频道需要一些新鲜的内容。
-Yeah, content. (SNIFFLES)
-Something.
- 是的，内容。(抽鼻涕)-一些东西。
-Rich, come on.
-Ooh!
- 瑞奇，快点-哦
Why don't you sing
that song with Freak-bot?
! 你为什么不和怪胎一
-Rich.
-Yeah!
起唱那首歌
-Come on, Barney. Do it.
-Rich, no.
? 瑞奇。
-Do it, do it!
-There isn't a song.
- 开枪啊开枪啊!-根本没有什么歌。
-BARNEY'S BOT: Incorrect.
-No. Shut up.
- 错误-不闭嘴。
It is by Zany Bogomil.
作者: 滑稽博戈米尔。
-Your grandmother's favorite.
-BARNEY: Stop!
- 你奶奶的最爱-别说了！
(SINGING) Dikky, dikky, dakka
Dikky, dikky, dikky dakka
(歌声)。 Dikky，Dikky，Dikky，Dikky
-Dikky, dikky, dakka
-(BOYS LAUGHING)
- Dikky，Dikky，dakka-(男孩笑)
-Dikky, dikky, dikky dakka
-Dude, come on, Barney.
- Dikky Dikky Dikky dakka-伙计别这样 Barney。
-You have to do it!
-Go on, man!
- 你必须这么做!
Can you guys
leave me alone, please?
-来吧伙计! 你们能让我一个
Yo, yo, yo, make him dance.
人静静吗? 哟哟哟让他跳舞。
No Miss Thomas here,
right, boys?
这里没有托马斯小姐，对吧，
I'm not...
No. I'm not gonna dance.
孩子们? 我不... 不，我不会跳舞的。
-(RICH WH|NES)
-Dikky, dikky, dakka
- Dikky，Dikky，
-Dikky, dikky, dikky dakka
-Okay, I got it. Shut up.
dakka-Dikky，Dikky，Dikky-好了，我知道了，闭嘴。
-(CONTINUES SINGING)
-RICH: Shut it now.
马上闭嘴。
I said shut it!
我说了闭嘴！
Shut up!
闭嘴！(停止唱歌
(STOPS SINGING)
))你为什么打
Why did you hit me?
我？因为我不
'Cause I don't like you,
derp-droid!
喜欢你，德普机器人
I don't like you, derp-droid!
！我不喜欢你，德普机
-RICH: Ow!
-Whoa.
器人！噢！哇。
What? Dumb bot.
- 什么?-笨机器人。
JAYDEN: Yeah.
ALEX: Yes!
- 耶耶-耶耶!-好耶
BARNEY: Okay, come on.
Let's. ..
! 巴尼: 好的，来吧，我们..。
(GROANS) B-Bots can't shove!
(GRUNTS)
B 级机器人推不动
(BOYSLAUGH)
(男孩笑声)
That's how you do... (GRUNTS)
你就是这么做的
Incorrect. I can shove with
a compressive force capacity
不对。我可以用压缩力量推
-of 29 pounds per square inch.
-(STIFLES LAUGH)
每平方英寸29磅
(COUGHS, GRUNTS)
(咳嗽声，咕噜声)
-(YELPS)
-Ooh.
哦。
My resin skin tenses on impact
to protect my CPU. Does yours?
我的树脂皮肤紧张的冲击，以保护我的中
All right, that's it!
I'm gonna destroy you!
央处理器。你的呢？好了，够了！我
-(BOYS CHEER)
-BARNEY: Oh, no.
要毁了你！哦，不。
Huh?
什么？
Yo. Why does it look
like that?
为什么是这个样子
I'm gonna destroy you.
? 我要毁了你。
-RICH: What's happening?
-I'm gonna destroy you.
- 发生什么事了?-我要毁了你。
Dude, seriously. Back off.
伙计，说真的，退后。
I'm gonna destroy you.
(GLITCHING)
我要毁了你
BARNEY: Hey, no! Stop!
巴尼: 嘿，不! 住手！
-RICH: Run!
-(BOYS WHIMPERING)
快跑
-I'm gonna destroy you.
-(LAUGHING)
我要毁了你
I'm gonna destroy you.
我要毁了你，我要毁了你。
Is this fun, Absalom?
这有意思吗，押沙龙？
-(LAUGHS) Yes! No.
-RICH: Help!
- 是的! 不是-救命！
ALEX: Oh, no.
BARNEY: Yes!
- 哦，不-是的！
-I'm gonna destroy you.
-(SCREAMS)
我要毁了你
RICH: Someone call the police!
里奇: 快叫警察！
RICH'S BOT: Contacting
local law enforcement.
瑞奇的 BOT: 联系当地执法部门。
-I am sorry, bro. Seriously!
-I'm gonna destroy you.
- 对不起兄弟说真的-我要毁了你。
-(RICH YELPS)
-I'm gonna destroy you.
我要毁了你。
-Cut the live stream!
-(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYS)
- 切断现场直播!-(嘻
(SCREAMING)
哈音乐)(尖叫)
Bros, it's pulling
my head off!
兄弟们，它把我的头扯
41 newtons.
下来了! 41牛顿。
-Bros!
-42 newtons.
- 兄弟们-42牛顿。
Hey,no,no,no!
You can't pull his head off.
嘿，不，不，不! 你不能把他的头扯下来。
-We'll get in trouble!
-(DINGS)
- 我们会有麻烦
-RICH: Help!
-Okay, Absalom.
的!-救命!-好的，押沙龙。
I cannot pull his head off.
我不能把他的头扯下来。
(CHUCKLES)
(笑声)
That's it. You are dead meat,
Pudowski!
够了，你死定了，帕多斯基！
ALEX: Dude, you are finished!
亚历克斯: 伙计，你完蛋了！
-Oh, yeah. We gotta run.
-ALEX: We're coming for you!
- 我们得走了-我们来救你了！
We gotta run right now!
我们现在就得跑！
Whoa! (LAUGHING)
哇! (笑)
(GRUNTS)
(咕噜声)
(LAUGHS) What?
什么？
Floor it!
加速! (笑)
(LAUGHING)
-喔呼!-
-Whoo-hoo!
-BOT: Whoo-hoo!
机器人: 喔呼!
(BARNEY GIGGLING)
(巴尼咯咯笑)
-(DING)
-(BOT LAUGHING)
- (叮)-(机器人笑
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
)(继续笑)-(机器
-(BOT STOPS LAUGHING)
-(LAUGHING)
人停止笑)-(
(BOTH LAUGHING EXAGGERATEDLY)
笑)(笑)(都夸张地笑)
That was awesome, okay.
太棒了。
But terrible, but awesome!
但是很糟糕，但是很棒! 我的意思是，
I mean, you can't hit people.
Especially Rich Belcher.
你不能打人，特别是里奇 · 贝尔彻。
But, oh, man!
You hit Rich Belcher!
但是，哦，伙计! 你打中了里奇 ·
I don't get it.
B-Bots can't hurt people.
贝尔彻! 我不明白。机器人不能伤害人。
They have mega safety controls
and stuff.
他们有巨大的安全控制和其他东西。
Incorrect. I have no mega
safety controls and stuff.
不对，我没有超级安全控制装置。
(CHIMES)
设置还
The settings
have not been uploaded.
没有上传。
What? Really?
(CHUCKLES) You're insane!
什么? 真的吗? 你疯了! 你要去哪儿?
Where are you going?
机器人:
BOT: To swap me
for a good one.
用我换一个好的。
No, no, no.
Hey, look. I've been thinking,
不不不听着我一直在想,
-and maybe I...
-(SIREN WHOOPING)
- 也许我...-
Freeze! I think it's him.
别动! 我想是他。
DISPATCHER: You gotta give me
a descr/ption, color
调度员: 你得给我一个解释
Yeah, uh-huh. White.
，颜色是的，嗯，白色。
-He/ght?
-Two foot tall.
- 他是谁?-两英尺高。
-Build?
-Yeah. Plastic.
- 建造?-是的，塑料的。
-Excuse me, sir?
-Whoa!
- 打扰一下先生
Easy.
?-哇! 别激动。
Okay. Both of you,
hands where I can see 'em.
好了，你们两个，把手放在我能看到的地方。
(OFFICER GASPS)
(警官喘气)
BOT: Dikky, dikky, dakka
Dikky, dikky, dikky dakka
机器人: Dikky，Dikky，dakka
OFFICER: Give it here!
Dikky，Dikky，Dik
GRAHAM:
That B-Bot is ours!
ky。军官: 给我！那个 b 机
OFFICER: It's a lunatic!
DONKA: It's just dancing.
器人是我们的！警官: 是个疯子！唐卡: 只是跳舞而已。
-I taught it.
-I paid for that.
- 我教的-我付的钱。
It was just doing what I said.
它只是照我说的做。
Take it away! It's crazy!
- 把它拿走! 太疯狂了!
BOT: At least
I'm not Uncle Boris.
-至少我不是鲍里斯叔叔。
I'm... I'm sure
it's just a minor issue.
我... 我相信这只是个小问题。
It's violent, uncontrollable,
and highly dangerous.
它是暴力的，无法控制的，高度危险的。
Okay, great.
Let me look into that.
太好了让我查查。
No. There's nothing wrong
with him.
不，他没有任何问题。
It assaulted a child!
它袭击了一个孩子!
It didn't assault him.
它没有袭击他。
I hit Rich Belcher.
It was awesome, but terrible,
我打了里奇 · 贝尔彻，很棒，但很糟糕,
-but awesome.
-See?
- 但是很棒-看到
-Barney... You were fighting?
-No!
没?-Barney... 你们在打架
(CHUCKLES) B-Bots
are incapable of violence.
?-没有! b 型机器人是不会暴力的。
BOT: Boink!
OFFICER: Officer down!
机器人: 砰! 警官: 警官中枪了
Bah, he had it coming.
! 呸，是他自找的。
You can'tjust take it.
It's mine!
你不能就这么拿走它是我的
I don't even know his name.
我甚至不知道他的名字。
Yes, you do! It's Absalom.
不，你知道，是押沙龙。
-Hi, Absalom.
-What?
- 你好押沙龙-什么
According to our records,
it has no registered owner.
? 根据我们的记录它没有注册所有人。
-But I give all my funeral money...
-Mom...
- 但我把我所有的葬礼费用...-妈妈..。
-...to that man in the alley.
-. . . please.
- 给巷子里的那个男人-拜托。
You got it
from a man in an alley?
你从一个在小巷里的男
Did you obtain
this bot illegally?
人那里得到的？你是非法获得
-What?
-(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
这个机器人的吗？什
This took a turn,
and we gotta get out of here.
么？情况变了，我们得离开这里。
Send it to the crusher!
- 把它送到碎石机去!-什
-What?
-For all we know,
么?-据我们所知,
-it could kill someone.
-(BOT DINGS)
- 会害死人
No. It's mine.
It was my birthday present.
的-不，这是我的，是我的生日礼物。
We'll return it
to the facility, run some tests.
我们会把它送回实验室做些测试。
Do you want me to close
the whole store?
你想让我关掉整个商
(GASPS) No, no, no.
Uh, one crushing coming up!
店吗? (喘气)不，不，不。嗯，一个粉碎
Use the recycler.
来了! 使用回收。
Adio's, Absalom.
再见，押沙龙。
Arrivederci. Auf Wiedersehen.
再见，再见。
No, you can't do that.
不，你不能这么做。
Dad, please.
It was sticking up for me.
爸爸，求你了，那是为了我。
Barney, we gotta let it go.
巴尼，我们得放手了。
OFFICER:
Let's take some details.
让我们谈谈细节。
-What was your name, sir?
-Uh. ..
- 你叫什么名字，先生?-呃..。
Absalom, will crushing be fun?
押沙龙，粉碎会
(GASPS)
很有趣吗
(喘气)
(GRUNTS)
(咕噜)
Phew.
呼。
-Hi, Absalom.
-Shh.
- 你好押沙龙-嘘。
-Happy birthday!
-What are you doing?
- 生日快乐!-你在干什么
A friend must stay
within six feet.
? 朋友必须待在6英尺以内。
We'll go
to the crusher together.
我们一起去破碎机。
No! Crushing is not fun!
It means smushed, flattened...
不! 压碎可不好玩! 它的意思是压碎，压扁..。
Uh...
呃..。
..A..
... a...
Think, think, think.
思考，思考，思考。
Annihilated.
毁灭。
(GASPS IN RELIEF)
(喘气救济)
-Annihilated. Not fun!
-Shh.
- 毁灭一点都不好玩!-嘘。
(WHISPERING)
We gotta get out of here.
我们得离开这里。
-Where are you...? Ow.
-(THUD)
你在哪
(HUMS)
里...
-Hey, stop! Hey!
-(PANTING)
? 我们得离
-(GASPS)
-We gotta get out of here.
开这里。
No. Come back.
不，回来。
-Whoa.
-Sorry.
- 哇-抱歉。
-(GASPS) Where are you going?
-You said, "Come back."
- 你要去哪儿?
(BARN EY GROANS)
-你说了
(GRUNTS)
”回来”
Sorry, again.
再次抱歉。
Bree, it got out!
布里，它跑出来了！
(BARN EY CHUCKLING)
(巴尼咯咯笑)
(WRESTLING BOT SHOUTING
IN SPANISH)
(摔跤机器人用西班牙语喊叫)
-Sorry!
-(EXCLAIMS IN SPANISH)
- 对不起!-(西班牙语惊叫)
-(WHISPERS) Where is it?
-BOT: Ayl
- 在哪里?-艾尔
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Lucha Iibre, third floor.
(紧张地笑) Lucha Iibre，三楼。
(BOTH PANTING)
停下!
-Stop!
-Oh, no.
-哦，不。
-(KIDS CHATTERING)
-BOY: Space! Final frontier!
太空! 最后的边界！
(BARN EY YELLS)
(巴尼大叫)
(CHUCKLES) Whew!
(咯咯笑)唷！
Uh-oh.
啊哦。
Follow me! (LAUGHING)
- 跟我来!-对不起，
Sorry, he's with me.
他是跟我一起的。
BOT 1: He is unaffected!
机器人1: 他不受影响!
BOT 2: Invincible one.
无敌机器人2:。
BOT 3: Space Lord.
BOT 3: 太空领主。
Hi, I am insane.
嗨，我是个疯子。
(SHRIEKS)
(尖叫声)
-Follow me.
-(BARN EY GRU NTS)
-跟我来。-(巴尼吼
(BARN EY YELLING)
叫声)(巴尼吼叫声)我
Are we having fun with me?
们在和我开玩笑吗？
You bet! (GASPS)
当然!
-(BOT WHIMPERS)
-(SHRIEKS)
布里:
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
你必须
BREE: You have to find it.
找到它。
It's gotta be here somewhere.
Keep looking.
肯定在这里的某个地方继续找。
-(SHOUTS IN SPANISH)
-BREE: Huh?
- 嗯?-他在
MAN: Where is he?
哪? 他
Where did they go?
们去哪了?
-(POP)
-BOT: Hi, I'm Sally Squirrel.
-嗨，我是萨莉松鼠。
(BOTS POPPING)
(机器人爆破)-厕
-Potty time! Sing with me!
-No! Shush!
所时间! 与我一起唱!-不! 嘘!
You are dead meat.
你是死肉。
MAN: Preschool forest.
学龄前森林。
BOTS: (SINGING)
Number one or number two
机器人: (唱)一号或二
Let’s learn
where we pee and poo
号让我们知道我们在哪里
Power down, power down!
撒尿和便便关机，关机！
Okay, everybody out.
Paws in the air.
好了，大家都出去，举起爪子。
-(SIGHS)
-I know you're in there.
我知道你在里面。
(BARN EY GASPS)
(巴尼喘气)
Ugh! Really.
真的吗。
-Barney!
-I'm sorry.
- Barney!-对不起。
(OFFICER GRUNTS)
(军官咕噜声)
How dare you! Are you
calling me a criminal?
- 你怎么敢这么说! 你是在说我是罪犯吗?
Mom, no, no, no.
You're not helping.
-妈妈，不，不，不，你在帮倒忙。
I paid for it!
我付钱了!-嗨，
-Hi, Absalom.
-BARNEY: Shh!
押沙龙。-嘘! 我带你回家
I'm gonna take you home, okay?
，好吗? 但是你
But you get
to choose your friends.
可以选择你的朋友。
And you don't choose me.
你没有选择我。
(CHUCKLES)
我知道
I do, okay. I choose you.
，好吧，我选你。
I can fix you, like Gran said,
我能治好你就像奶奶说的,
and I'll teach you
how to be my friend.
我会教你怎么做我的朋友。
Okay, Absalom.
好吧押沙龙。
Okay.
好吧。
My registered name is Absalom,
我的名字是押沙龙,
but my friends call me Barney.
但朋友们都叫我巴尼。
(DINGS)
我的朋友
My friends call me...
都叫我..。
Ron Bintscatsco.
罗恩 · 宾斯卡斯科。
(CHUCKLES) Okay, Ron.
好吧 Ron。
Okay, Barney.
好了，巴尼。
DONKA: One day parking ticket,
唐卡: 一天的停车罚单,
-next day firing squad.
-(GASPS)
- 第二天行刑
GRAHAM: No, that's not
gonna be a problem.
队-不这不成问题。
Hey, Barn. I am so sorry
about the B-Bot.
巴恩 b 机器人的事我很抱歉。
I'll figure something out.
我会想办法的。
It's okay, Dad. Not a problem.
没关系，爸爸，没问题。
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
我...
I... Ithink
it's gonna be fine.
我想会没事的。
PEOPLE: 93, 94, 95, 96,
人: 93,94,95,96,
97, 98, 99!
97,98,99！
-(ALL CHEERING)
-(ANDREW CHUCKLING)
- 卖出了一亿
One hundred
million units sold!
套! 哇! 耶
Whoo! Yeah!
! 我们
Well, we made
100 million new friends,
交了一亿个新朋友,
all helping kids connect,
meet each other,
所有帮助孩子们相互联系，相互认识,
-interact.
-And all through their B-Bots.
- 互动-通过他们的 b 机器人。
Making friends face-to-face?
面对面交朋友? (嘲笑
(SCOFFS)
So last three millennia.
)三千年过去了。
(CHUCKLES) That's not what...
不是这样的..。
Some kids check in
with their bots
一些孩子每天要向他们
a hundred times a day,
plus 11 times overnight.
的机器人报到100次，外加一夜之间的11次。
We've finally done it.
We've ended sleep.
我们终于做到了，我们结束了睡眠。
Uh, the algorithm
may need adjusting.
算法可能需要调整。
ANDREW: Think of the data
we can harvest!
安德鲁: 想想我们可以收集的数据! 不，不，
No, no, no. I designed them...
不，我设计了它们... ..。
-In my garage.
-. . .for making friends.
- 在我的车库里-为了交朋友。
Into dollars.
换成美元。
If our share price
goes any higher,
如果我们的股价再上涨,
we'll have to give it
a space suit. (SLURPS DRINK)
我们必须给它一套太空服。
So what about the B-Bot
that punched a child?
(啧啧喝)那么那个打小孩的 b 机器人怎么样
(CAMERA CLICKING)
? (摄像机咔哒声)
It hit a cop?
- 打中了一个警察
And a child.
?-还有一个孩子。
It hit a cop.
We can't put that on the box.
它撞到了警察我们不能把它放在盒子上。
No, no. B-Bots are incapable
of violence.
不，不，b 机器人不会使用暴力。
My algorithm
totally ensures no...
我的算法完全保证没有..。
OFFICER: 0W/ 0W/
RICH: 0W/ 0W/
0W/0W/RICH: 0W/0W/
-I better look into that.
-You think?
- 我最好调查一下-你这么认为？
I mean, what if someone
gets injured?
如果有人受伤了怎么办？
I, for one, could not live
就我而言，我无法生存
with what that would do
to our share price.
这会对我们的股价造成什么影响。
BREE: it’s not a problem.
这不是问题。
We performed a complimentary
in-store crushing.
我们进行了免费的店内粉碎。
Good! Uh...
很好。
Because if that
was still out there,
因为如果那东西还在的话,
we'd be toast.
我们会被烤熟的。
-(CHICKENS CLUCKING)
-Shh. Guys, no clucking.
嘘，伙计们，不要咯咯叫。
Okay, Ron.
How to be my friend.
好吧，罗恩，怎么做我的朋友。
A bunch of your code
is missing, right?
你的一堆代码不见了，对吧?
The settings
have not been uploaded.
设置还没有上传。
So, I'm gonna teach you
to be my friend.
所以我要教你怎么做我的朋友。
And then
you can come to school.
然后你就可以来学校了。
What is a friend, Barney?
- 什么是朋友 B
Well, a friend
is a person who, uh,
arney?-朋友就是..,
Hkes,uh_.
哈哈。
ls always... I...
总是... 我..。
A person who, uh, "likes,
is always, I."
一个”喜欢的人总是我”好吧，
Okay.
Now I'm your best friend.
现在我是你最好的朋友了。
(CHUCKLES) Hey. Come back.
嘿，回来。
No, no, no. There's a lot more
than that, Ron.
不，不，不，还有很多，罗恩。
You have to know
everything about me.
你必须了解我的一切。
You have to like me,
obviously.
显然，你必须喜欢我。
Like all the same stuff as me,
and you have to be on my side.
和我一样，你必须站在我这边。
But don't hit people.
Even Rich Belcher.
但是不要打人，包括里奇 · 贝尔彻。
Hair, brown. Height, 4'11".
头发棕色身高4英尺11英寸。
5'11" would be better.
You could reach high objects.
5英尺11英寸更好，你能够到高处的物体。
Hey. (CHUCKLES) A friend likes
everything about you.
- 嘿-朋友喜欢你的一切。
-What?
-Let's go to school.
- 什么?-我们去学校吧。
(LAUGHS) You don't even know
where school is.
你连学校在哪都不知道。
Alice Springs, Allahabad,
Anchorage, Albuquerque.
爱丽丝泉，阿拉哈巴德，安克雷奇，阿尔伯克基。
Ooh. A-ha!
哦，妈妈!
Mom! You're shorting
the power out!
你把电源弄短路了
(MOTIVATIONAL MUSIC PLAYING)
! (音乐声)
(LAUGHING)
(笑)
You gotta fit in.
你得融入进去。
Huh?
嗯? 喜欢
Likes. Rocks, chess, Pac-ll/lan.
石头象棋吃豆子。
-Bill the Bus.
-No!
- 比尔巴士-不
That was when I was,
like, two.
那是我两岁的时候。
Toast. But only for breakfast.
烤面包，但只能当早餐。
(SLURPS) Butter on its own.
黄油本身就是黄油。
RON: Mm!
罗恩:
(LAUGHS)
嗯!
(DONKA EXCLAIMS, TSKING)
(笑声)
(WASHING MACHINE WHIRRING)
不喜欢负
(GRUNTING SHAKILY)
鼠、音乐剧
Dislikes. Possums,
musicals, school. Generally.
、学校。一般来说。
The BuddyBench.
兄弟长凳。
Eugh! Worms. I don't trust
anything without a face.
啊! 虫子。我不相信没有脸的东西。
-(SHRIEKS)
-(BOTH LAUGH)
- (尖叫)-(笑声)
Stop!
住手!
I am fitting in!
我正在适应！
You must always stay
within six feet.
你必须一直呆在6英尺以内。
I will always stay
within six feet.
我会一直呆在6英尺以内。
Unless I say not to.
除非我说不要。
I am not to stay
within six feet.
我不能待在六英尺以内。
No, no. Sometimes, yes.
不不有时候是的。
-Sometimes.
-And sometimes, no.
- 有时候-有时候不是。
-Yes.
-Like, if I had a bad day
- 是的-比如，如果我有一个糟糕的一天
-or. ..
-Bad day. Always six feet.
-或者...-糟糕的一天，总是六英尺。
(LAUGHING)
(笑)谷仓:
BARN EY: Allergies.
Goats, wool. Goats' wool.
过敏，山羊，羊毛，山羊毛。
I'm basically
allergic to life.
我基本上对生活过敏。
That's why I like rocks.
这就是为什么我喜欢石头。
That is sad and also tragic.
这是悲哀的，也是悲剧的。
What are you into, huh?
Electricity?
你喜欢什么? 电?
Electricity is better
than rocks.
电比石头好。
Ron, what are you...
罗恩，你在..。
(LAUGHING)
(笑
(LAUGHS MOCKINGLY)
声)
Whoo-hoo-hoo! You got it!
You got the six feet!
你成功了，你有六英尺高！
Hey! No, no, no. That's...
嘿! 不不不那是..。
-GRAHAM: Barney?
-(GASPS)
- 巴尼?-
I got a little break.
You wanna do something?
我有点休息，你想做点什么吗
Chess, maybe?
? 比如下棋？
Uh, thanks, Dad. I'm good.
谢谢，爸爸，我很好。
Okay.
好吧。
-(CHUCKLES)
-(MOTIVATIONAL MUSIC RESUMES)
- (轻声笑)-(音乐继续)
(IMPERCEPTIBLE)
(不易察觉)
BARN EY: Rocks.
RON: Electricity.
伊恩: 石头。罗恩: 电。
BARN EY: Rocks are better.
巴尼: 石头更好。
RON: Electricity.
BARNEY: Uh, I said rocks.
罗恩: 电。巴尼: 嗯，我说的是石头。
RON: I prefer electricity.
罗恩: 我更喜欢电。
-Rocks. (LAUGHING)
-RON: Electricity.
- 石头-电流。
List friends.
列出你的朋友。
Uh, next question.
下一个问题。
(RON DINGS)
你知道，我..
You know, I'm... I'm not
actually unpopular, you know.
. 我并不是不受欢迎的，你知道。
That would mean
they know I exist.
那就意味着他们知道我的存在。
-RON: Perhaps you don't.
-Hey!
- 罗恩: 也许你不知道
RON: List relations.
-嘿! 罗恩: 列出关系。
Dad, Donka,
some Bulgarian uncles.
爸爸 Donka 还有几个保加利亚的叔叔。
Donka says, actually,
one was possessed,
唐卡说，事实上，有一个人被附身了,
but I think it might
have been a nut allergy.
但我觉得可能是坚果过敏。
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(忧郁的音乐播放)
There was Mom, too, of course.
当然，还有妈妈。
But, uh,
she died when I was two.
但是我两岁的时候她就去世了。
And Dad moved us out here.
爸爸把我们搬到这里。
It doesn't make me sad exactly
'cause I... I can't remember.
这并不让我伤心，因为我... 我记不起来了。
But it did make
things hard for Dad.
但这确实让爸爸很为难。
She was returned
to the facility?
- 她被送回监
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
I guess. No receipt.
狱了?-我想是的，没有收据。
(DINGS)
每天抓
Scratches neck
14.5 times a day.
脖子14.5次。
-What are you doing?
-I am learning about my friend.
- 你在干什么?-我在了解我的朋友。
Oh, cool.
哦，酷。
Please slap my hand
to show we are bonding.
请拍拍我的手，表示我们是一体的。
Oh! Okay. (CHUCKLES)
哦！好吧。你睡着了
(POWERS DOWN)
！没有。
You went to sleep!
这是一个举动
-No. It was a move.
-(LAUGHS)
。我现在是你最好的
Am I now your best friend
out of the box?
朋友了吗？你不会还想
You're not still
after that sticker.
要那张贴纸吧。
(BOTH LAUGHING)
哦，不，罗恩
(GASPS)
，对不起，
Oh, no, Ron. I'm so sorry.
Hold on. Hold on.
等等，等等。
-RON: Connect. Connect.
-No! Stop! (GASPS)
罗恩: 连接，连接。-不! 停下!-哦
-Oh, no! Not that one! Ron!
-Connect. Connect. Connect.
，不! 不是那个! 罗恩!-连接，连接，连接。
That's Savannah's house!
那是萨凡纳的房子! 好的，
Okay, key light,
Malibu filter.
钥匙灯，马里布过滤器。
-Perfect.
-GIRL: Boom!
- 太好了-砰
Oh, hey, guys.
! 嘿，伙计们。
You just caught me chilling.
你刚好撞见我在发抖。
-(RON LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
-(BOTH SHRIEKING)
水上的，
-(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
-RON: Afloat. Aquatic.
水上的。
Accident.
意外。
-(SOFT BURST)
-(BOTH GASPING)
那是什么？听起
(HEAVY WHEEZING)
来像一条巨蛇。
What is that?
或者一个
It sounds like a giant snake.
Or an evil clown!
邪恶的小丑！他们住在树
They live in the woods,
林里,
and their heads go
all the way around!
而且他们的头一直绕着
-(CONTI N U ES WH EEZI NG)
-(BOTH SHRIEKING)
！- 邪恶的小丑！邪恶的小丑！
-Evil clown! Evil clown!
-BARNEY: Sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起。对不起。
I'm just really wheezy, guys.
I've been running.
我只是有点喘，伙计们，我一直在跑步。
Ron! (SCREAMS)
罗恩!
(BOTH YELP)
(尖叫声)
Barney Pudowski?
巴尼 · 普多斯
-(FLOAT SQUEAKING)
-(WHIMPERING)
基?-(花车吱吱声)-(
(BOTH GASP)
呜咽声)(喘
You've ruined my aesthetic.
息声)你毁了我的美学。
Sorry, Savannah.
(COUGHS) Nice pooI.
抱歉，萨凡纳漂亮的泳池。
Wait. Since when
did you even have a B-Bot?
等等你什么时候开始有机
And... Whoa. Look at him.
器人了看看他。
I'm sorry. We're going
right now. Ijust...
对不起，我们现在就走，我只是..。
Barney, your B-Bot is,
like, super weird.
Barney 你的机器人超级奇怪。
GIRL: Yeah.
SAVANNAH: And naked?
- 是啊-还是裸体的？
GIRL: Ew!
女孩: 呃！
And hold on a sec.
Why hasn't it friended me?
等一下，为什么它没有加我好友？
Would you like to friend
@theSavannahMeads?
你愿意加@the avannahmeads 为好友吗？
BARNEY: No. He can't do
any of that stuff.
不，他什么都做不了。
He can't make friends or...
He's useless at all that.
他交不到朋友或者... 他一点用都没有。
-(GASPS) Can't make friends?
-GIRL: What?
- 不能交朋友吗?-什么? B
Barney,
don't say your weirdness
arney 别说你
has rubbed off on him.
的古怪影响了他。
Making friends is, like,
what he's for.
交朋友就是他的职责所在。
If he can't do that, he's,
like, literally pointless.
如果他做不到，他就毫无意义了。
Like, a lump of plastic
just following you around.
就像一团塑料围着你转。
Hashtag landfill.
标签垃圾填埋。
-I am for making friends?
-BARNEY: Ron...
- 我可以交朋友吗?-罗恩..。
How do I make friends
for Barney?
我怎样才能和巴尼交朋友呢
BARN EY: Come. (SCREAMS)
? 巴尼: 来吧。
-Senouﬁy?
-Ugh.
(尖叫)-塞努菲?-呃。
You share stuff about him.
你们分享他的故事。
Like pictures of his food
or his wake-up routine.
比如他的食物照片或者他的叫醒程序。
You search
for people who know him
你寻找那些认识他或
or like the same stuff as him.
者喜欢和他一样东西的人。
You show them pictures,
and then you get comments,
你给他们看照片，然后得到评论,
and then you get
people that like him,
然后你找到喜欢他的人,
and then you get
friend invites.
然后你就会收到朋友邀请。
-Boom! Now he has friends.
-Duh!
- 嘣! 现在他有朋友了-切!
Ron! We have to go!
Ron! 我们得走了!
Does Barney need friends?
Barney 需要朋友
Well, yeah! Or, fun fact,
吗? 是的! 或者有趣的事实是,
he will not survive
middle school.
他活不过中学。
Savannah,
please don't tell anyone.
萨凡纳，请别告诉任何人。
I'm not supposed to have him.
He has to be a secret.
我不应该拥有他，他必须是个秘密。
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(忧郁的音乐播放)
(SIGHS)
(叹气)(
(MUFFLED RATTLING)
低沉的卡嗒声)
(GRAHAM SPEAKING SPANISH)
她在重接
She's rewiring los electricos.
电线。
Okay. Unicorn poo.
好吧，独角兽便便。
-(TOY SQUEAKS)
-(CHUCKLES)
- 太棒了
-It's great.
-(MAN ON PHONE SPEAKS SPANISH)
-你喜欢!
You like it!
Well, shipping date, um...
好吧，装运日期，嗯..。
Ow! It shocked me!
噢! 吓死我了！
(BEEPS)
(哔哔声
(CHUCKLES)
)(笑声)
Mind if I leave it on?
介意我开着吗？
(SIGHS)
罗恩:
RON: I am literally pointless.
我真的毫无意义。
What?
什么? 我
I cannot make friends for you.
不能为你交朋友。
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Yeah. Well...
是啊，好吧..。
I'm not so great
at that either.
我也不是很擅长这个。
You should see me
during recess. Oh, it sucks.
- 你应该在休息的时候来看看我-糟透了。
I stand there every day,
我每天都站在那里,
on my own,
on the edge of the yard,
我一个人在院子边上,
just hoping for a few people
to share a bench with.
只是希望能有几个人和我一起坐在长椅上。
You know?
但是他们
But why would they?
为什么要这么做呢？
The last time any of them
came to my house,
他们最后一次来我家,
we set fire to them.
我们放火烧了他们。
-(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
-GRAHAM: Ow! Not again.
噢! 又来了。
-(SWITCH CLICKS)
-(SIGHS)
我想我还是睡觉
I guess I'll just
sleep with it off.
的时候把它关掉吧。
Good night, Ron.
晚安，罗恩。
(TENDER MUSIC PLAYING)
(温柔的音乐播放)
AN DREW: They’re psychos/
德鲁: 他们是疯子/(
(SHRIEKING AND YELLING)
尖叫和叫喊)就是
It is them! I'd recognize
those ears from space.
他们! 我从太空中就能认出这对耳朵。
Okay. Location. GPS.
Uh... Get up the grid.
好的位置 GPS 呃... 打开网格。
Where is it?
- 在哪儿?
Uh, it's not actually
on the network.
-呃实际上不在网上。
That's impossible.
So, I don't believe you.
这不可能所以我不相信你。
We track every B-Bot.
我们追踪每一个 b 机器人。
-Um, yeah, but...
-Then the kid.
- 是的但是...-然后那个孩子。
I want everything. Contacts,
shopping habits, shoe-size.
我什么都想要，联系人，购物习惯，鞋码。
You mean his private data?
你是说他的私人数据? 当然。
Sure.
Why else do we collect it?
不然我们为什么要收集它? 我
We've got nothing on him.
He hasn't friended anyone.
们没有他的把柄。他没有加任何人为好友。
He doesn't blog, post,
or share.
他不写博客，不发文章，也不分享。
Creepy.
真恐怖。
The video was posted
by @theSavannahMeads.
该视频由@The avannahmeads 发布。
Her whole life is online.
她的整个生活都在网上。
Andrew. Is it true?
It's still out there?
安德鲁。这是真的吗? 它还在那里
The store made an error.
They squished Sally Squirrel.
? 商店犯了一个错误。他们压扁了莎莉松鼠。
SALLY SQUIRREL: (SINGING)
Let’s learn where we...
萨莉松鼠: (唱)让我们知道我们在哪里..。
-(POWERS DOWN)
-That's awesome!
太棒了! 你到
What the heck
are you talking about?
底在说什么
I looked into it. And...
? 我查过了。
(BARNEY AND RON LAUGHING)
看到了吗? 就是
See? This is it!
这个! 这就是我在
It's what I imagined
when I was his age.
他这个年纪时的想象。
They're having fun!
- 他们玩得很
Fun?
开心-开心？
How... How can you
have fun offline?
怎么... 怎么能在线下找乐子呢
It's against nature.
? 这违背自然规律。
Andrew, I never programmed
B-Bots to laugh.
安德鲁，我从来没有给 b 机器人编程让他们笑。
I have to understand this.
Can we get a hold of it?
我必须理解这一点。我们能得到它吗？
Ho-ho, we will.
我们会的。
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(不祥的音乐播放)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
我的天线
My aerial?
No power in whole street?
? 整条街都没电
No. No idea.
? 不知道。
What? Ron, no! You have to hide.
什么? 荣恩，不! 你得躲起来。
You're not ready.
你还没准备好。
(SIGHS) I'm sorry. I'll be back soon.
对不起，我很快就回来。
(SCOOTER SQUEAKING)
(踏板车吱吱声)
(GRUNTS)
(咕噜声)
There are no friends in the shed.
小屋里没有朋友。
-Hi! I am Barney's B-Bot.
-(CAR HORN HONKS)
- 嗨! 我是巴尼的 b-
I live in the shed.
机器人-我住在小屋里。
-I am for making friends.
-MAN: Idiot!
我是来交朋友的。白痴
I am sharing Barney's
breakfast. Do you like it?
！我要分享巴尼的早餐。你喜欢吗？你
-(DOG BARKS)
-How about you?
呢？(狗嗅，WH
(DOG SNIFFS, WH|NES)
| NES)
Would you like to comment
on this picture, old woman?
老太太，你对这张照片有什么看法吗
Barney likes rocks, asthma inhalers,
and his grandmother's food.
? 巴尼喜欢石头、哮喘吸入器和他祖母的食物。
Will you come to my secret
shed and like him?
你会来我的秘密小屋喜欢他吗?
(GRUNTS NERVOUSLY)
(紧张地咕
No. No, no. No.
哝)不，不，不，不。
Barney likes rock hammers, too!
巴尼也喜欢石锤! 我
(IMITATES BARNEY) I'm gonna be late.
要迟到了。
My pants are on backwards.
我的裤子穿反了。
That was Barney's wake-up routine!
这是巴尼的叫醒程序!-
-Okay.
-Friend request.
好的。-好友申请。
Friend request.
好友请求。
MISS THOMAS: So a prime number
托马斯小姐: 所以
is a natural number
greater than one
质数是一个自然数，大于不
that cannot be divided
by any number.
能被任何数除的数。
-(GASPS)
-I know you're keen,
我知道你很热心,
but it's not quite recess yet, Barney.
但还没到休息的时候，巴尼。
(BREATHLESSLY) Oh, my asthma.
I need my inhaler, ma'am.
(喘气)哦，我的哮喘。我需要我的吸入器，女士。
Uh, I'll be one minute.
一分钟就好。
(GASPS)
(喘气)
Ron! What are you doing here?
罗恩! 你在这里干什么?
There are no friends in the shed.
棚子里没有朋友。
I am for making friends.
我喜欢交朋友。
No! No, no, no. You have to go
before they come out for...
不! 不，不，不，你必须在他们出来之前离开..。
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
课间休息。
Recess.
(STUDENTS CHATTERING)
(学生交谈声))机器人:
BOT: You have two new messages.
你有两条新信息。
GIRL: Only two?
女孩: 只有两个? 嘿，
Hey, Barn. You got a B-Bot?
巴尼，你有 b
-Hey.
型机器人吗?-嘿。
Awesome.
太棒了。
Huh. Well, that went well.
哈，很好，很顺利。
I thought so.
我想也是。
Okay.
好吧。
Come on.
来吧。
Wow, that's so minimalistic.
It's like a blank canvas.
哇，这太简约了，就像一张空白的画布。
-Friend request.
-(BARNEY CHUCKLES)
好友
(CHATTERI NG CONTI N U ES)
请求
Recess.
休息。
Maybe it'll be okay.
也许会好起来的。
Recess will not suck.
课间休息不会很难受。
You will have friends
to sit with on a bench.
你会有朋友和你一起坐在长凳上。
I don't know. Yeah. I guess.
- 我不知道-我想是的。
RON: You will.
罗恩: 你会的。
-I have brought you some.
-What?
- 我给你带了一些-什么
I am literally not landfill.
? 我可不是垃圾填埋场。
(STUDENTS CHEERING)
(学生欢呼)-(舞曲
-(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
-GIRL: This is so crazy.
播放)-女孩: 这太疯狂了。
(GASPING)
罗恩
Ron! Wait!
!
(CHEERING)
等等
You have five new friends.
你有了五个新朋友。
I did a search for them.
我搜索了一下。
Shayne likes low-priced alcohol
and conspiracy theories.
尚恩喜欢低价酒和阴谋论。
He believes there's
a secret lizard government
他相信在瑞士地下有一个
-beneath Switzerland.
-Shh.
秘密的蜥蜴政府。
He will friend you
if he can stay in the shed.
如果他能呆在小屋里，他会加你为好友的。
Barney! Bro! Just for a year. Two max.
巴尼，兄弟，就一年，最多两年。
Are those your friends,
Barney?
那些是你的朋友吗，巴尼?
Is this, like, a rave?
这是一个狂欢派对吗
This friend shared
your breakfast and liked it.
? 这个朋友分享了你的早餐，而且很喜欢。
Oh, yeah!
罗恩: 他
RON: He gets hungry like you.
和你一样饿了。
Your neighbor Mrs. Baxter's parrot
has one friend in common with you.
你的邻居巴克斯特夫人的鹦鹉和你有一个共同的朋友。
Your neighbor, Mrs. Baxter.
你的邻居，巴克斯特夫人。
-He commented on your photo.
-(PARROT SQUAWKS)
他评论了你的照片。(鹦鹉嘎
He has done other things
on your photo, too.
嘎)他还对你的照片做了其他的事情。
Margaret will friend you
玛格丽特会加你为好友并分
-and share her...
-No.
享她的... 不。
(IMITATES MARGARET)
...purse, watch, anything
钱包，手表，任何东西!
it! please, please just let her go.
求你了，求你放了她吧。
Now you have friends to
sit with on a bench at recess.
现在你有朋友可以在课间休息时和你一起坐在长凳上。
I'm so sorry.
You can't be here.
对不起，你不能来这里。
(BABY COOING)
巴尼，
Barney, meet friend number five.
这是我的第五个朋友。
This tiny bald man
likes your picture so much,
这个小秃头很喜欢你的照片,
he is eating it.
他在吃。
There he is! Logan!
他在那儿，洛根！
Friend request, friend request.
好友请求，好友请求。
-Ron?
-STUDENTS: Ron, Ron, Ron.
- 荣恩?-荣恩，荣恩，荣恩。
-Yeah! Come on!
-ALL: Ron, Ron, Ron!
- 耶! 加油!-Ron Ron Ron Ron Ron!-Sa
BREE: Savannah Meads' mom
didn't recognize the boy.
vannah Meads 的妈妈没认出那个男孩。
We're at her school now.
我们现在在她的学校。
Okay, sure.
好的，当然。
We keep this low-key, people. Discreet.
我们要保持低调谨慎。
Nice and quiet, okay?
安静点，好吗?-爱你们
-Love you guys!
-STUDENTS: Ron, Ron, Ron.
!-学生: 罗恩，罗恩，罗恩。
Pudowski!
帕多斯基!-(无
-(CHUCKLES HELPLESSLY)
-Yeah!
助的笑声)-是的!
Sticking it to the man!
粘住他! 校长办公室
Principal's office. Now!
。现在!-(叹气声)-
-(SIGHS)
-(BABY COOING)
(婴儿咕咕声)(
(BABBLES PLAYFULLY)
开玩笑地)
RICH: Hey, bros. Ho-ho-ho-ho.
里奇: 嘿，兄弟们。
(CHUCKLES)
快点，
Come on, Pudowski. Move it!
帕多斯基，快点!
(BOYS LAUGHING)
你不是新来的
You're not new, are you?
吧? 你就是那个
You're that crazy broken dude
who punched me.
打我的疯子。
How'd you do that?
- 你怎么做到
I have no mega safety controls
and stuff.
的?-我没有超级安全控制装置。
Safety settings, parental controls,
account limits, all off!
安全设置，父母控制，帐户限制，所有关闭！
That's how come he hit you, dude!
这就是为什么他会打你，伙计！
I want mine like that.
Then it can hit me, too!
我想要我的那样，那么它也可以打击我！
I could get R-rated movies.
我可以去看 r 级电影。
Copy him. Find that code.
收到，找到密码。
RICH'S BOT: Unlock.
理查的 BOT: 解锁。
BOTS: Unlock.
机器人: 解锁。
He's gonna get us a trillion views!
他会给我们带来一万亿的点击量! (兴奋地
(ALL CHUCKLE EXCITEDLY)
咯咯笑)-(男孩们的笑
-(BOYS LAUGHING)
-ALEX'S BOT: I don't like you.
声)-亚历克斯的机器人: 我不喜欢你。
RICH'S BOT: I don't like you.
我不喜欢你。
-(ALEX YELPS)
-(RICH CACKLES)
- (亚历克斯 · 耶尔普斯)-(瑞奇 · 卡克尔斯)
-(GASPS)
-(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
- (喘气)-(男人说隐约)
Hey, guys.
嘿伙计们。
Savannah. What's going on?
萨凡纳，发生什么事了?
(GASPS EXCITEDLY) It's Bubble!
(兴奋地喘气)这是泡泡
My post is such a hit,
the whole company's following me.
! 我的帖子太火了，整个公司都在跟踪我。
What post?
什么邮件? 两
Twenty thousand friends love...
万个朋友的爱..。
(ALL SHRIEKING AND YELLING)
什么? 我
What? I said he has to be a secret.
说他必须是个秘密。
I know. But it went crazy!
我知道，但是它疯了
(SHUDDERS)
! 你真
You're such an actual freak, Barney,
是个怪胎，巴尼,
it's, like, almost cool.
简直酷毙了。
(CHUCKLES DRYLY)
克里弗先生:
MR. CLEAVER: Pudowski!
帕多斯基!-
-(GASPS)
-Pudowski! What is going on?
帕多斯基! 怎么回事？
Nothing, Ms. Hartley.
没什么 Hartley 女士。
You brought in a baby?
你带来了一个婴儿? 人
Artificially sweetened beverages?
工甜味饮料?-一只鹦鹉。
-A parrot.
-一只鹦鹉。
-(FUMBLES)
-Where is the bot?
- 机器人在哪儿?
(MUFFLED YELLING)
-给总部
(GASPS) Call head office.
打电话。
-(BOYS LAUGHING)
-Get him, boys.
抓住他，伙计们。
(CROWD CHEERS)
机器人:
BOTS: Unlock, unlock, unlock.
解锁，解锁，解锁。
Get 'em!
抓住他们!-(机器
-(BOT YELLS)
-(BOYS YELP)
人大叫)-(男孩大叫)
BOT: Unlock.
NOAH: Uh...
- 解锁-呃..。
Okay. Buy 10,000 mechbucks.
好吧买一万块。
Whoa! It works!
BubbIePay has no limits!
哇! 成功了! BubbIePay 没有极限
Give me weapons. Give me upgrades.
! 给我武器，给我升级。
BOT: All upgrades unlocked.
机器人: 所有升级解锁。
Hey! Jerk of Thrones.
嘿! 《权力的混蛋》。
-What?
-Get them!
- 什么?-抓住他们!
Hey! Those are our bots!
嘿! 那些是我们的机器人
-Give them back!
-NOAH: Whoa!
!-还给他们!-
BOT: Levelling up!
哇! 升级!-哇!-我
-NOAH: Whoa!
-My prank, Noah.
的恶作剧，诺亚。
Thanks for the ride. Oh!
谢谢你载我一程
Rich, come back!
。哦! 瑞奇
RICH: Yo, Sav. Who's lame now?
，回来! 瑞奇: 哟，萨维。
-Hey!
-Unlock.
现在谁是瘸子?-嘿!-开锁。
Do you wanna connect
你想连接到所有
to all the users
of the Bubble network?
的 Bubble 网络
You can access them all?
Um, yeah!
的用户吗？你可以全部访问吗？嗯，
Okay, hi, um, everyone in the world.
是的！好的，嗨，嗯，全世界的人。
This is @theSavannahMeads.
这是@the avannahmeads。
And this is
Nonsuch Middle School.
这是一所普通中学。
(RICH WHOOPING AND LAUGHING)
(富人的欢呼声和笑声)
-(LAUGHS)
-BOY: lncoming/
-(笑声)-男孩: 来
(YELPS)
了/(叫喊声)
It's Mad Max meets
Sesame Streetlive streaming.
这是《疯狂的麦克斯》和《芝麻街直播》的结合。
We think the safety controls
are off on all the bots.
我们认为所有机器人的安全控制都是关闭的。
Uh, let's send out a patch.
我们发个补丁吧。
Yeah, we're on it!
好的我们
(BREE YELPING)
这就去！学生:
STUDENT: That was awesome!
太棒了！-
-What the. . .?
-(ALL GASP)
这是...
BOT 1: You shall not pass.
？你们不能通过。
BOT 2: KiSS my Sith Lord butt!
机器人2: 亲我的西斯尊
BOT 3: Rabbits, attack!
主的屁股! 机器人3:
Destroy! Destroy! Destroy!
兔子，攻击! 毁灭! 毁灭!
(STUDENTS SCREAMING
AND LAUGHING)
毁灭! (学生尖叫和大笑)
Book a party at a night club.
在夜总会预定一个聚会。
Invite everyone. Except Savannah.
邀请所有人除了萨凡纳。
Everybody, stop!
所有人，停下!
Hey, Rich!
嘿，瑞奇!
-Whoo-hoo-hoo!
-JAYDEN: Catch!
-呜-呼-呼!-杰登: 接着！
Whoo! (LAUGHS)
喔！你在现场直播吗，
You got this on the live, bro?
兄弟？(机器人
(BOT GROWLING)
咆哮)为了看风景！所
For the views!
以这基本上是一种
So it's basically kind of
the apocalypse, but fun!
天启，但是很有趣！嘿，住手，
Hey, cut it out, Sav. This is my thing.
萨维。这是我的事。
Sorry, Rich. I have...
抱歉瑞奇我得..。
Four million, four hundred
and thirty-two views.
400万，432次浏览。
Oh, Australia ’s waking up.
G’da y, guys.
哦，澳大利亚醒了，大家好。
We're about to be shamed
by a whole other hemisphere.
我们即将被另一个半球羞辱。
SAVAN NAH :
l’m @theSa vannah/l/leads.
我是@theSa vannah/l/leads。
And this is a giant monkey. ..
这是一只巨大的猴子..。
zombie mash-up that’s
basically trashing our school.
僵尸混搭，简直就是在毁掉我们的学校。
-Patch in one minute.
-Are you knitting this thing?
- 一分钟内补好-你在编织这东西吗？
-Do something!
-MARGARET: Hello?
- 做点什么!-喂？
It's nearly pickup!
快好了！
BOT: Brains!
机器人: 大脑！
(MARGARET YELPS)
玛格丽特 · 耶尔普斯
Ha-ha/ And l’m Rich Belcher
from Prank You Very Much.
哈哈/我是《非常爱恶作剧》里的 Rich Belcher。
Get this.
听听这个。
SAVANNAH: Hey, hey.
(SCREAMING)
萨凡纳: 嘿，嘿。
RICH: Snack!
(尖叫)
(ALL GASP)
里奇: 吃点
(SAVAN NAH SH RI EKI NG)
东西! (喘息)(萨万那那
(SAVAN NAH GRU NTI NG)
那那那那那那)(萨万那那
(YELPS)
那那那那)(吼
(GRUNTS)
)(咕哝)
It pooped me.
它让我筋疲力尽。
BOT 1: Sharing "It pooped me."
BOT 1: 分享“它让我大便失禁”BOT 2: 分享“
BOT 2: Sharing "It pooped me."
BOTS: Sharing.
它让我大便失禁”BOTS: 分享。
-No. Stop it.
-Shanng.Shanng.Shanng.
- 不，住手-珊，珊，珊。
-Don't share that.
-Sharing "It pooped me."
- 不要分
MARC: Uploading the patch now!
享-分
(BOTS POWERING DOWN)
享“它让我
(YELPING)
精疲力尽了
(GRUNTING)
”马上上
That's the patch.
传补丁。
Just in time.
Good thing nobody saw it.
来得正是时候幸好没人看见。
You just killed Bubble, Marc.
你刚刚杀了 Bubble Marc。
Spread out. Find the rogue.
散开，找到那个流氓。
How can I put this gently? Get out!
我该怎么说才好呢?
(BARNEY SIGHS)
出去
-Hi, Barney.
-(BARNEY GROANS)
- 嗨 BARNEY
We have 43 new friends.
-我们有43个新朋友了。
Maybe you do.
But I've been kicked out.
也许你知道，但是我已经被踢出来了。
(BEEPS)
这边请。
-(DOOR OPENS)
-MAN: This way.
Ugh!
啊！
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(忧郁的音乐播放)
How could you? You dumb bot!
你怎么能这样? 你这个笨机器人!
I'm in so much trouble now.
我现在有大麻烦了。
All you had to do was just fit in.
你所要做的就是融入其中。
What was the point of even. . .?
... ...
RON: Barney, are you my friend?
有什么意义？罗恩:
What?
巴尼，
What do you mean?
你是我的朋友吗？
My dad bought you for me.
什么？什么意思？我爸爸给我买了你。
What's that?
那是什么？
Where are you going?
你要去哪里?
Friendship is a two-way street.
友谊是双向的。
-What?
-RON: I get to choose.
- 什么?-我来选择。
-(TIRES SCREECH)
-You taught me.
是你教我的。
BARNEY: I didn't say
be more than six feet.
巴尼: 我没说要超过六英尺。
RON: But you are having a bad day.
罗恩: 但是你今天过得很糟糕。
You know what? I don't care.
Fine! Go on then.
- 你知道吗? 我不在乎-好吧那你去吧。
-RON: I am going.
-Uh-huh.
罗恩: 我要走了。
-RON: Okay.
-Okay. I'll...
- 罗恩: 好的-好的，我会..。
-RON: Okay.
-Okay!
罗恩:
(CRASHING)
好的-好的
(SIGHS)
罗恩: 阿迪奥的，
RON: Adio's,
registered-name-Absalom.
登记的名字，押沙龙。
Adio's, Absalom's B-Bot.
再见，押沙龙的 b 机器人。
(GRUNTS IN FRUSTRATION)
(沮丧的咕哝声)斯泰西: 这在
STACEY: It's trending
in 13 countries!
13个国家都成了热门话题! 克雷格:
CRAIG: They've searched
the school, Marc.
他们已经搜索了学校，马克。
They didn't find it.
他们没有找到。
BOT: Bubble shares
are crashing. Down 43%.
机器人: 泡沫股票正在崩溃，下跌了43% 。
We've got thousands of parents
complaining about B-Bot safety.
我们有成千上万的家长抱怨 b- 机器人的安全性。
We've got thousands of kids complaining
their bots won't do the same stuff!
我们有成千上万的孩子抱怨他们的机器人不
Marc, what do we do?
能做同样的事情! 马克，我们
I... Uh, I've...
该怎么办? 我... 呃，我..。
ANDREW: I wonder.
安德鲁: 我想知道。
(SLURPING LOU DLY)
也许一个用滑板交
Maybe being a guy who makes
his friends out of skateboards
朋友的人，并不足以让你运营
doesn't equip you to run
a global tech giant.
一家全球科技巨头。
-(SKATEBOARD CLATTERING)
-Mm!
- (滑板声)-嗯! 好吧
Okay. Here's our story.
，这就是我们的故事。
We blame everything on the rogue.
我们把一切都归咎于这个流氓。
A single unit with a minor coding error.
一个编码错误很小的单元。
Minor? But the riot.
未成年? 但是暴乱。
What riot? We hose down the Internet.
什么暴乱? 我们把互联网洗劫一空。
Delete every video.
Take down every post.
删除所有视频，删除所有帖子。
Any TV station broadcasts it,
任何电视台都会播放,
we buy the station and
replace it with cat videos,
我们买下电视台，用猫咪视频取而代之,
then we sue the kids
for misuse of product
然后我们控告这些孩子滥用产品，除非
unless they sign a binding yada, yada,
他们签署一个约束性的什么什么的,
and send the principal a fruit basket.
给校长送个水果篮。
But what does the genius think?
但是这个天才怎么想
(SIGHS) Okay. Andrew, you do this.
? 好吧，安德鲁，你来做这个。
Sweetjustice pie.
甜蜜的正义派。
Hey, run off back to your lab
嘿，滚回你的实验室去发
and invent something
that doesn't kill us all.
明一些不会杀死我们所有人的东西吧。
And, uh, you got an algorithm
for refilling this?
你有算法来补充吗？
We got an address from the school.
我们从学校得到了地址。
Pudowski. Oak Hill Drive.
Pudowski 橡树山大道。
Bing bong belushi!
乒乓贝鲁西！
Huh? (SIGHS)
- 嗯?-没有但
GRAHAM: No. But Barney
doesn't even have a B-Bot.
Barney 连个机器人都没有。
BREE: All the kids at school
confirm he does, Mr. Pudowski.
布里: 学校里所有的孩子都证实了这一点，普多斯基先生。
He started a riot.
他发动了一场骚乱。
I'm sorry, are you calling
my son a liar?
对不起，你是
-DONKA: Oh, Barney.
-(SIGHS)
说我儿子是
(DOOR CREAKS)
个骗子吗
(CLUCKING)
?-哦
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
，巴尼
RON: Barney, are you my friend?
罗恩: 巴尼，你是我的朋友吗?
(MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING)
(忧郁的音乐响起)巴尼
BARN EY: ”Know everything about me. ”
: “了解我的一切。”
”Sta y within six feet of me. ”
“站在离我六英尺的地方.”
”Like me. ”
”像我一样”
(SIGHS)
-
-(PLASTIC SQUEAKING)
-Huh?
嗯?-
(GASPS) Ron!
罗恩！
What are you doing?
- 你在干
Returning myself
to the facility.
什么?-把我送回实验室。
I am a dumb bot.
我是个哑巴机器人。
No! No, you're not. I'm so sorry.
不! 不，你不是，我很抱歉。
(SIGHS) I was wrong.
我错了。
We did not fix me. I did not fit in.
我们没有治好我，我不适合这里。
Who cares? Neither do I.
谁在乎呢? 我也不在乎。
It doesn't matter.
'Cause you are my friend.
没关系，因为你是我的朋友。
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(感伤的音乐播放)
Your best friend out of the box?
你最好的朋友从盒
(CHUCKLES)
子里出来
(UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING)
(令人振奋的音乐播放)
(CHUCKLES)
(笑声)
But still don't burn
my underpants. (CHUCKLES)
不过别把我的内裤给烧了。你知道
GRAHAM: You know, I have been
worried about him, but, uh,
，我很担心他，但是，呃,
I just... I work these crazy hours.
我只是... 工作时间太长了。
BREE: The bot's in there?
机器人在里面?
Okay. This thing is dangerous.
好吧，这东西很危险。
We need to destroy it.
我们必须摧毁它。
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
我们
-Let's run.
-GRAHAM: Barney,
跑吧,
-are you in there?
-(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
- 你在里面吗
Just you and me.
?-只有你和我。
GRAHAM: Mom, do you have a key?
妈妈，你有钥
-We don't need anyone else.
-(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
匙吗？我们不需要
Hey, you're not in trouble.
Please, just let me in.
其他人。嘿，你没有麻烦。求你了让我进去吧。
(CHICKEN CLUCKS)
他在
(GASPS) Where is he?
哪里
-(CHICKENS CLUCKING)
-(BARN EY GRU NTI NG)
?-嘘，
-Shh.
-No clucking.
别叫。
BREE: Could he be with a friend?
布里: 他会
Well, he...
he doesn't really have any.
和朋友在一起吗? 嗯，他... 他没有朋友。
(SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(感伤的音乐播放)
-(BARN EY GRU NTI NG)
-(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
- (谷仓的声音)-(物体的碰撞声)
MAN: Hey! Isn't that the kid?
嘿! 那不是那个孩子吗？
BARNEY: Go! Go, go, go!
走! 走，走，走！
MAN: He's getting away!
男人: 他跑了！
(GRUNTING)
We need to go faster!
我们得再快点！
No problem!
没问题！
(BARN EY YELLS)
(巴尼大叫)
Ron, you did it! Yes!
(CHUCKLES)
罗恩，你成功了!
(GASPS, YELLS)
太好了
Hey, down here!
嘿，下来! 嘿，
MAN: Hey, stop! Come back!
We just want the bot!
停下! 回来
(PANTING)
! 我们只
Quick! (YELPS)
想要机器人
(ELECTRONIC TRILLS)
! 快点
Shh.
! 嘘。
"Poop Girl" is trending.
You have 19,032,000 likes.
“大便女孩”成为热门话题，你获得了1903.2万个赞。
(SAVANNAH SOBBING)
- 他往这边
MAN: He went this way!
RON: Shh.
走了!-嘘。
Hey, miss. You seen a boy and a bot?
小姐，你看见一个男孩和一个机器人了吗？
Do I look like I care?
我看起来像在乎的人吗？
Okay, sorry. My bad.
好吧，对不起，我的错。
What's going on?
- 怎么了?-Bu
Bubble are looking for Ron.
bble 在找 Ron。
They blame him for the riot.
I have to protect him.
他们把暴乱归咎于他我必须保护他。
MAN: Hey, dude.
I think that was Poop Girl.
嘿，伙计，我想那是便便女孩。
(MAN LAUGHS)
萨凡纳?
-(SAVAN NAH SOBS)
-Savannah?
“大便女孩”有两千
"Poop Girl" has 20 million and 56...
万和五千六百万..。
Poop Girl. That's...
大便女孩，那是..。
That's who I'm gonna be
for my whole life.
我这辈子都会是这样的。
BARN EY: No.
巴尼: 没有。
MAN 2: You sure
he's not back there?
你确定他不在后面?-
-We gotta go.
-Wait.
我们得走了-等等。
You're running away?
To the woods?
你要逃跑? 去森林?
Please don't tell anyone this time.
这次请不要告诉任何人。
There are evil clowns
in there, Barney.
里面有邪恶的小丑，巴尼。
Their heads go
all the way around.
他们的脑袋到处乱转。
That's owls, Savannah. I promise!
那是猫头鹰，
(BARNEY WHOOPING AND LAUGHING)
萨凡纳，我保证
You lost them? No, no, no.
This is not happening.
- 你跟丢了?-不不不这不可能。
You know what?
你知道吗进入城
Access the cameras
on every B-Bot in town.
里所有 b 机器人的摄像头。
Use B-Bots to spy?
使用机器人侦察? 不，
No. We're just recording
for training and monitoring purposes.
我们只是为了训练和监视的目的而录音。
-But Marc would never...
-Marc put a camera
- 但马克绝不会...-马克在全
within six feet of every
young consumer in the country.
国每个年轻消费者身边都安装了摄像头。
And now you're worried about privacy?
现在你又开始担心隐私了?
Turn on the mics, too.
把麦克风也打开。
Listen out for "Barney," “Rogue Bot,"
听听“巴尼”“流氓机器
"Profit-sucking plastic
psycho." That kind of thing.
人”“利润吸吮塑料精神病”之类的。
We'll find him. Wherever he is
in that Podunk town!
我们会找到他的无论他在哪个小镇！
(SCOOTER SQUEAKING)
(摩托车吱吱声
-Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
-RON: Whoo-hoo.
)-呜-呼-呼-呼!-罗恩: 呜-呼。
(UPTEMPO MUSIC PLAYING)
(快节奏的音乐)
(LAUGHS)
)(笑声
(WHOOPING)
))(呜呜声))(
(BOTH GRUNTING SHAKILY)
都是咕噜声))
(LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY)
(歇斯底里地笑声)
Whoo! (ECHOES)
喔! (回声))
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(笑声))(BA
(BARNEY YELLING AND GRUNTING)
RNEY 大叫和咕哝)
(SIGHS CONTENTEDLY)
(心满意足地叹了口气)
Whoo. (CHUCKLES)
- 喔-罗恩
-Ron. (LAUGHING)
-RON: In yourface.
-当着你的面。
(IMITATES LIGHTSABER)
(模仿光剑)来吧
Come on, Space Lord, fight me!
(IMITATES GUNSHOT)
，太空领主，跟我打! (模仿枪声)你
You need a stick.
需要一根棍子。
-Searching for stick.
-Huh?
- 在找棍子-啊?-
-Is this one good?
-(SCREAMS)
这个好吗?-
Come back
and let me hurt you.
回来让我揍你。
Ron! That's way too big
for a stick!
罗恩! 那对于一根棍子
Look at mine compared to yours!
来说太大了! 看看我的和你
-RON: Please help.
-(LAUGHS)
的!-罗恩: 请帮帮忙。
You have 0.85 friends.
-(笑声)你有0.85个朋友。
-You have 0.7 friends.
-Oh, wow, you're sinking.
- 你有0.7个朋友-你在下沉。
Hold on. Just... (GASPS)
等等你有0.2
You have 0.2 friends.
个朋友。
Grab my hands!
I'm gonna get you out.
抓住我的手! 我会救你出去的。
我会救你出去的。
(BARNEY GROANING AND SPITTING)
(巴尼呻吟和吐痰)-(乐观的音
-(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
-(BARNEY SIGHS, SPITS)
乐播放)-(巴尼叹气，吐痰)
You know what? You choose.
你知道吗? 你选吧。
Two-way street, right?
双行道，对吧?
That way is good.
那边很好。
No, wait, wait.
Where are you going?
不，等等，你要去哪里？
Ron. Hey, wait.
Stop! Stop, stop.
罗恩，等等，停下，停下。
(BARN EY GASPS)
不! 罗
No! Ron!
恩! (紧张地
(GRUNTING NERVOUSLY)
咕哝着)(咯咯声
(YELLS)
，咳嗽声)
(GURGLES, COUGHS)
，抓住你了
Gotcha! Whoa!
! 哇！
-(GASPING HEAVILY)
-RON: Gotcha!
抓到
(BARNEY COUGHING)
你了
What? Why on earth
would you do that?
什么？你到底为什么要这么做？我必须
Do I have to like the path you like?
喜欢你喜欢的道路
No! (COUGHS, SPITS)
But your path sucks!
吗？不！(咳嗽，吐痰))但是你的
(COUGHING) And seriously?
Off a cliff?
路糟透了！(咳嗽)真的吗？掉下悬
I like,
崖？我喜欢,
"Seriously?
(COUGHING) Off a cliff?"
“真的吗? (咳嗽)掉下悬
That way is good.
崖?”那样很好。
-(HEAVY WHIRRING)
-Log.Log.
- (沉重的呼呼声)-原木。原木。
-Log.
-(CHUCKLES) Here.
- 木头-给你。
(GRUNTS)
你吃太多
Been eating
too much electricity?
电了?-你的肌
-Your muscles are under-sized.
-No, they're not.
肉太小了-不，没有。
(UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING)
(令人振奋的音乐播放)
Hey, Ron.
嘿，罗恩。
Tell me something about you.
I never asked.
告诉我一些关于你的事情，我从来没有问过。
I am a Bubble generation one B-Bot.
我是一个泡泡一代一个 b 机器人。
I currently have one friend.
我现在只有一个朋友。
Oh, wow. I found it.
(BLOWS) Nice!
- 我找到了-不错！
You wanna share?
你想
-(CHOMPING)
-(BARNEY LAUGHS)
分享吗
You have not shared
29 friend invites.
你没有分享29个好友邀请。
Yeah. I know.
我知道。
If you don't ask, they can't say no.
如果你不问，他们就不能说不。
Problem solved.
问题解决了。
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(忧郁的音乐播放)
You know who I had at my party
when I was six?
你知道我六岁的时候在派对
Savannah and Rich. For real.
上有谁吗? 萨凡纳和里奇，真的。
They were my friends just
because they lived nearby.
他们是我的朋友，仅仅因为他们住在附近。
But at some point you just...
You just get it...
但在某种程度上你只是... 你只是得到它..。
that you're not gonna be
one of the cool kids.
你不会成为那些酷孩子中的一员。
Hey, who cares, right?
嘿，谁在乎呢，
'Cause I currently have
one friend, too. (CHUCKLES)
对吧? 因为我现在也有一个朋友
How long will we live in the woods?
- 我们要在树林里
I don't know. (CHUCKLES)
住多久?-我不知道
Forever?
永远？
(BARN EY CH UCKLES)
你知道什
(YAWNS)
么故事吗
Do you know any stories, Ron?
，罗恩? 我可以
I can create one
from my available data.
用我现有的数据创造一个。
It will be called
它将被命名为
"The Awesome Adventures
of Absalom of Addis Ababa
“亚的斯亚贝巴的阿布沙
"and His Android, Alan."
龙和他的机器人艾伦的
(CHUCKLES)
可怕冒险”
Once upon a time in Addis Ababa,
很久以前在亚的斯亚贝巴,
capital city of Ethiopia,
sovereign state in the Horn of Africa,
埃塞俄比亚首都，非洲之角的主权国家,
with 100 million inhabitants,
拥有1亿居民,
lived Absalom and his friend Alan,
a generation one android.
住着押沙龙和他的朋友艾伦，一代机器人。
(CHUCKLES)
That's a nice story.
真是个好故事。
(YAWNS)
(YAWNS
(TENDER MUSIC PLAYING)
)(温柔的音乐播放)
BOT: Shall we check your
messages one more time?
机器人: 我们要不要再检查一下你的信息? 女孩:
GIRL: Yeah, sure.
BOT: ”Poop Girl” is trending.
好的，当然。机器人: “大便女孩”正在流行。
GIRL 2: Savannah
unfriended me ? Unfriend her/
女孩2: 萨凡纳解除我的好友关系? 解除她/男
BOY: Well, anyone with a brain cell
should block Rich Belcher.
孩: 好吧，任何有脑细胞的人都应该阻止里奇 · 贝尔彻。
BOT: Message to
anyone with a brain cell.
机器人: 给任何有脑细胞的人发信息。
7'he y what? it wasn ’t my fault.
什么? 那不是我的错。
BOT: Shall we check your
messages one more time?
机器人: 我们要不要再检查一下
MARC: My algorithm. What?
你的信息? 我的算法。什么？
GIRL 1: Did you see Savannah?
你看到萨凡纳了吗？大便女孩，
GIRL 2: Poop Girl, r/ght?
对吧？女孩3: 我很高
GIRL 3: l’m so glad
/ am not her r/ght now.
兴/现在不是她的生日。
BOY 1: You dropped her
from this chat, r/ght?
男孩1: 你把她从聊天室里扔出去了，
BOT: Dropping Savannah
from this chat.
对吧?-把萨瓦娜从聊天室里扔出去了。
GIRL 4: Someone did a remix.
女孩4: 有人重新混音了。
-(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
-(SINGING) ltpoopedme
这是谁做的
lt pooped me
?
(GASPS) Who did that?
是匿名创
Anonymouse3 created it.
造的。
23 million friends love
"Poop Girl, the Remix!"
2300万朋友喜欢“大便女孩，
-(WHIMPERS)
-(DOORBELL RINGS)
混音版!”
Hi. Uh, we're Barney's...
嗨我们是 Barney 的..。
-He hasn't come home.
-(GASPS)
- 他还没回家-是
And, yeah. So we're just...
啊所以我们只是..。
We're checking with his, uh...
(CLEARS THROAT)
我们正在和他的...
his fellow children.
他的孩子们核实。
You are Barney's friend.
你是巴尼的朋友。
You come to his birthday party.
你来参加他的生日派对。
My goat eat your slap bracelet.
我的羊吃了你的手镯。
Oh! That party.
哦! 那个派对。
Do you have any idea where he is?
你知道他在哪儿吗？
Uh...
呃..。
No, I, uh... Sorry.
不，我，呃... 对不起。
(SIGHS)
(叹气)
Oh, Mom. I work round
the clock selling novelty junk
哦，妈妈。我日以继夜地卖新奇的垃圾，
just to try to give him a life.
只是为了给他一个生活。
But I'm blowing it, Mom.
I... I've lost touch with him
但是我搞砸了，妈妈，我... 我和他失去
Why didn't he come to me?
了联系他为什么不
Sometimes kid protect grown-up.
来找我，有时候孩子会保护大人。
That's not right.
这是不对的。
He will be okay.
他会没事的。
Pudowskis are brave and strong.
普多斯基既勇敢又强壮。
(DISTANT SCREAMING)
(远处的尖叫
(SCREAMING MANIACALLY)
)(疯狂的尖叫
(WHIMPERING)
)(呜咽)
There's a spider.
Literally, like, this big!
有一只蜘蛛，真的有这么大! 一只
A bird has commented on your face.
鸟在你脸上留言了。
Oh, great.
太好了。
Where even are we?
我们到底在哪里? (
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
学校铃响)
Recess. Now known as
20 minutes of extra math.
课间休息。现在被称为20分钟的额外数学。
BOT 1: What is four-fifths as a decimal?
十进制的五分之四是什么？
-BOT 2: What is the square root of nine?
-BOY: Ugh! Seriously?
- BOT 2:9的平方根是多少？啊
You have to be kidding me.
！真的吗？开什么玩笑。
RICH: Alex, Jayden!
里奇: 亚历克斯
Yesterday was sick, right?
，杰登! 昨天病了，
Sorry. Jayden's not available right now.
对吧? 抱歉，杰登现在不在。
They've blocked me?
他们屏蔽了我? 机器
BOT: Simplify the expression:
人: 简化
three to the power of eight
minus eleven.
表达式: 3的8次方减去11。
Rich!
有钱! 两千五百
Twenty-five million friends love...
万朋友的爱..。
-/t pooped me
-Wait! Seriously!
- 我累坏了-等等! 说
-You have ruined my life.
-Uh...
真的!-你毁了我的生活。
But, look. It's Barney, okay?
He's missing.
但是，听着，他是巴尼，他失踪了。
What?
什么? 你和我，
You and me, we got him in trouble.
我们给他惹了麻烦。
He's in the woods.
It's our fault he's out there.
他在树林里，他在外面都是我们的错。
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(雷声隆隆)
(BARNEY PANTING TIREDLY)
(巴尼喘着粗气)
RON: Access denied.
RON: 访问被拒绝。
-BARNEY: Here. (GRUNTING)
-Access denied. Access...
- 这里-拒绝访问访问..。
Access.
访问。
Let's find some place to camp.
我们找个地方扎营吧。
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(雷声隆隆)
(GROANS) Everything's wet.
所有东西都湿了。
How long is...
多长时间..。
(IMITATES MOCKINGLY)
"I don't know. Forever"?
(模仿嘲笑)“我不知道
Twelve hours?
Twelve days? Twelve years?
，永远”? 12个小时? 12天? 12
-Twelve decades?
-Stop asking dumb questions.
年?-12年?-别再问愚蠢的问题了。
I have 12% battery power remaining.
我还有12% 的电池电量。
Ron, come back.
(GRUNTS IN FRUSTRATION)
罗恩，回来。你的大脑受
Have you got water damage
to the brain?
到水的伤害了吗？
I mean, seriously?
我是说真的吗
If you go back, they will
send you to the crusher.
？如果你回去，他们就会把你送进粉碎机。
Do you want to be recycled
as a lunch box?
你想被回收成为一个午餐盒
What is your plan? Is it,
吗? 你的计划是什么,
"Run! Run away!
“快跑! 快跑!”-“快，快，
-"Go, go, go! We gotta run."
-Stop. Ron.
快! 我们得快跑。”-停，罗恩。
Stop it!
住手! 89%
Avoids problems 89% of the time.
的时间都在回避问题。
You are so annoying!
你真烦人! 你
You are so annoying 43.8% of the time.
有43.8% 的时间都很烦人。
(GRUNTS IN FRUSTRATION)
(沮丧的咕哝声)
Why don't you save your battery
by getting off my back?
)你为什么不从我的背上下来省省你的电池？
Argh. There's nothing
in these woods that'll burn!
啊，这树林里没有什么东西会烧起来的！
Incorrect.
不正确。
(LIGHT MUSIC PLAYING)
(轻音乐响
(SPUTTERS, LAUGHS)
起))哈
Ha-ha-ha-ha. (GASPS)
哈哈哈哈
(LAUGHS)
(笑)
What's that?
- 那是什么?
(CHUCKLES)
I never told you that.
-我从没告诉过你。
I'm not afraid of the dark.
我不怕黑。
(WARNING TONE BEEPING)
哦，不，
Oh, no. Ron.
罗恩。
My solar battery function
我的太阳能电池功能
(DISTORTED)
has not been uploaded.
(失真)还没有上传。
(GASPS) Electricity.
Of course you like it.
电力，你当然喜欢。
Five percent battery remaining.
电池剩余5% 。
Five percent? Uh...
百分之五。
Okay. Go to sleep.
Power down. Power down.
好了睡觉吧关掉电源关掉电源。
(POWERS DOWN)
(电源关闭)
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(忧郁的音乐播放)
-(BRANCHES CREAKING)
-(SHUDDERING)
-(树枝吱吱作响)-(颤抖)
Oh, Ron. You're right about the dark.
哦，罗恩，你对黑暗的看法是对的。
After my mom died, I was
terrified every single night.
我妈妈去世后，我每天晚上都很害怕。
And I wanted so bad
我太想跑进
to just run into my dad's room
and tell him...
我爸的房间告诉他..。
but what if
he was scared, too?
但如果他也
-(POWERS DOWN)
-(GASPS)
害怕呢?-
Ron!
罗恩！
Seriously, Ron?
真的吗，罗恩？
-(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
-(LEAVES RUSTLING)
没人知道我们
No one even knows we're here.
在这里。
He’s in the woods.
it’s our fault he ’s out there.
他在树林里，他在外面都是我们的错。
He left town for the woods?
他离开小镇去森林了? 现
It's night. The weather's getting worse.
在是晚上，天气越来越糟了。
Pff. So access the security cameras.
那就进入监控录像。
There aren't any. It's the woods.
根本没有，是树林。
Insane. Okay.
疯了好吧。
Let's put some in.
我们放一些进去吧。
MARC: Get me to Nonsuch.
马克: 带我去诺萨基。
They're in the woods.
I have to meet Ron and Barney.
他们在树林里，我得去见罗恩和巴尼。
(BARN EY GRUNTING TIREDLY)
(巴恩的喘气声)
One of these trees must have
a power outlet or something, right?
这些树中肯定有一棵有电源插座什么的，对吧
(SIGHS)
Oh, this is not okay, Ron.
? (叹气)哦，这可不行，罗恩。
Best friends don't die on each other.
最好的朋友是不会死在一起的。
(PANTING)
我们是在
Are we going around in circles?
绕圈子吗？
(GASPS)
嘿! 这
Hey! Down here! Over here!
Help us! Help!
里! 这里! 救命! 救命！
Wait. They'll help me, but...
等等他们会帮我但是..。
No, no, no. Come on. (GRUNTS)
不，不，
(PANTING AND WHIMPERING)
不，来吧
(SHUDDERING)
(颤抖)
What are they?
他
(GASPS)
们
(YELLS)
是
(PANTING)
什
Ow. (GASPING)
么?
(YELLS, GRUNTS)
噢
(GASPS WEAKLY)
(喘气声)
I got nothing.
我一无所获。
We can't give up.
我们不能放弃。
People get lost in those woods
and never come out.
人们在那片树林里迷了路，再也出不来了。
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(紧张的音乐播放)
You know what?
你知道吗？
We've done our best.
Let's call it a night.
我们已经尽力了今晚就到此为止吧。
-What? We can't do that.
-But what about the boy?
- 什么? 我们不能这么做-
He's just not in there.
那孩子怎么办? 他不在里面。
We should try across town tomorrow.
我们明天应该去城那边试试。
Let's all go home.
我们都回家吧。
(GROANS WEAKLY)
(呻吟)(
(BARN EY GASPS)
巴尼喘气)
(WHEEZING)
(喘息)巴尼:
BARN EY: That's Savannah's
B-Bot. And Noah's.
那是萨凡纳的 b- 机器人，还有诺亚的。
(GASPS AND COUGHS)
罗恩，罗恩，罗恩，罗恩，罗恩
(INHALER SPRAYS)
，罗恩，罗恩，罗恩
(COUGHS)
，罗恩，罗恩，
Ron. (WHEEZES)
罗恩，罗恩，罗恩，罗恩，罗恩
(BUZZING)
，罗恩，罗恩，罗恩，
(WHEEZES)
罗恩，罗恩，罗恩，罗恩，罗恩，
I guess we're both literally landfill.
罗恩，罗恩，罗恩，罗恩，罗恩。
-(CONTINUES WHEEZING)
-(BUZZING)
- (继续喘息)-
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
(紧张的音乐播放)
(BEEPS)
(哔哔声)
-(SIGHS)
-(BOT TRILLS)
“便便女孩”
"Poop Girl" has 32 million...
有三千两百万..。
Why is there mud on your wheels?
为什么你的车轮上有泥巴？
Huh?
嗯? (
(SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
轻柔的戏剧音乐播放)
(PANTING WEAKLY)
不，不，
No, no. You can't go back.
(COUGHS)
你不能回去
Must survive middle school.
必须在中学毕业后生存下来。
No, no, Ron. They'll... (GASPS)
不，不，罗恩，他们会...
They'll take you forever.
他们会永远带着你。
(BARN EY WH EEZI NG)
他们会把你
They'll send you to the crusher.
送到破碎机那里。
(COUGHS) Stay with me.
坚持住。
There are no friends in the woods.
森林里没有朋友。
BARN EY: Ron.
巴尼: 罗恩。
SAVAN NAH: What is it?
这是什么? 机器人: 警
BOT: Alert Bubble.
Alert Bubble. Alert Bubble.
告泡泡，警告泡泡，警告泡泡。
SAVANNAH: Do you see that?
Oh, my gosh!
萨凡纳: 你看到了吗? 我的天啊! 气
BOT 2: Bubble Bot,
Ron Bintscatsco...
泡机器人，罗恩 · 宾斯卡斯科..。
-It's Ron.
-RICH: Hey! It's him!
- 是罗恩-嘿! 是他！
-And... And Barney!
-RICH: Barney?
- 还有... 还有 Barney!-Barney？
(PANTING) Barney! Come on!
巴尼! 快点！
We're coming, brother.
Hang on there!
我们来了兄弟坚持住！
-Barney, are you okay?
-Barney!
- Barney 你没事吧?-Barney！
It's his asthma.
He can't breathe right.
是他的哮喘他不能正常呼吸。
BOT: Twelve-year-old boy.
Grade two bronchospasm.
十二岁男童，二级支气管痉挛。
(BARN EY WH EEZES)
你们为什
(WEAKLY)
Why are you guys here?
么来这里?
FHends_.
(DISTORTED) Sixth birthday.
六岁生日。
(WHEEZES) Sorry.
(喘息))对不起。
He thought that... I... I know...
他以为... 我... 我知道..。
(GASPS HEAVILY)
我知道你们
I know you're not my friends.
不是我的朋友。
(GASPING RAGGEDLY)
我们不
Well, we're not not your friends.
是你的朋友。
-(WHEEZING)
-(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
- (喘息声)-(直升机呼呼声))(孩子
(KIDS GASP AND EXCLAIM)
们喘气和惊叫声))萨凡纳:
SAVANNAH: Over here!
在这里! 里奇: 哟，
RICH: Yo, guys, he's over here.
伙计们，他在这里。
-Get down here. Let's go!
-(SIREN WAILING)
- 下来，我们走!-
SAVANNAH: He's hurt.
He needs help.
他受伤了，他需要帮助。
-Quick! It's them. Help them!
-MAN: Okay, I can see them.
- 快，是他们，救救他们!-好，我看到他们了。
GRAHAM: Barney! Oh, Barney!
- 巴尼! 巴尼!
SAVANNAH: Mr. Pudowski,
Mr. Pudowski, he's over here.
-帕多斯基先生，他在那边。
RICH: Check his lungs
for a pulse or something.
里奇: 检查他的肺部有没有脉搏什么的。
-Stand back!
-DONKA: Oh, my Barney.
- 退后!-哦，我的巴尼。
All right, deep breaths.
好了，深呼吸。
-GRAHAM: Everything's okay. Dad's here.
-DONKA: Help him, please!
- 没事了，爸爸来了-救救他!-我
WOMAN: We've located the kid.
们找到那孩子了。
SITA: It's them! They're safe.
是他们! 他们很安全。
-TECH: They found them!
-(STAFF CHEERING)
- 他们找到他们了!-怎
-What's happening?
-The bot saved the boy.
么回事?-机器人救了那个男孩。
What? That evil profit-sucking thing!
什么? 那个邪恶的利润吸盘!-抓住它!
-Grab it!
-/’m on it.
-我这就去。
-Stand back.
-He y. .. Let me take him.
- 退后-让我来。
-Give me the bot.
-SAVAN NAH: What are you doing?
把机器人给我。你在干什么
-Stop! You can't take him!
-NOAH: Leave him alone!
？住手！你不能带走他！放
-SAVAN NAH: Stop it!
-It's dangerous.
开他！住手！太危险了。
-He's not dangerous.
-RICH: No!
- 他不危险-不! 你不
You can't take him. We won't let you!
能带走他，我们不会让你带走的!
That bot is Barney's best friend, dude.
那个机器人是巴尼最好的朋友，伙计。
-He just saved his life!
-(WHIRRING)
- 他刚刚救了他的命!-(呼呼声)-(停
-(WHIRRING STOPS)
-(KIDS GASP)
止呼呼声)-(孩子喘气)-哦，不。
-Oh, no.
-JOSH: The stream's trending.
-乔希: 小溪的趋势。
People are calling the bot a hero!
人们称这个机器人为英雄！
Brave Bubble Bot saved boy.
RIP, Ron. How sad.
勇敢的泡泡机器人救了男孩。安息吧，罗恩。真悲哀。
-And yet how great for sales!
-What?
- 但是销量还是很不错
Okay. Moving on!
的!-什么? 好吧，继续！
(SIGHS)
我们从小
We've known Barney
since we were little.
就认识 Barney。
You were his best friend
in kindergarten.
你是他幼儿园时最好的朋友。
And you were mine.
而你是我的。
It gets complicated.
事情变得复杂了。
Yeah, right.
Should I friend Barney?
是啊，我应该加巴尼为好友吗
Searching for "Barney likes pranks."
? 搜索“巴尼喜欢恶作剧”，
No matches.
没有匹配。
-Your pranks are lame.
-They're funny, man.
- 你的恶作剧太差劲了-很有趣伙计。
Ifl don't do funny, uh, I got nothing.
如果我不搞笑的话，我就什么都没有了。
Since when did this stuff matter?
- 什么时候开始这事重要了
Barney and Ron. It's like we used to be.
?-Barney 和 Ron 就像以前一样。
-(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYS)
-SAVAN NAH: lt pooped me
它把我拉屎了(音乐停止)
(MUSIC STOPS)
-(BAR
(SIGHS)
NEY 咕
-(BARNEY GRUNTS)
-(BOTH GASP)
哝)-(喘气)
-Barney? Barney!
-DONKA: Oh, Barney!
-BARNE
Hey! Oh, Barney, I am so sorry.
Y？巴尼！哦，巴尼！嘿！巴尼，我很抱歉。
I let you down.
我让你失望了。
(MUFFLED MUMBLING)
我知道我总
I know I'm always
overwhelmed with work.
是被工作压得喘不过气来。
-But I'm your dad, okay?
-(SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
- 但我是你爸爸好吗?-你
You're like a piece of my heart
就像我心中的一块碎
walking around the world,
片在世界上游走,
and I love you so much
我是如此的爱你，这让我有
that it makes me strong enough
to deal with anything.
足够的勇气去面对任何事情。
Except losing touch with you.
除了和你失去联系。
(SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
跟我说话
Just talk to me, Barney.
，巴尼。
-BARNEY: I'm trying!
-You're lonely? I get it.
- 我在努力!-你很孤独? 我明白。
-BARNEY: Where's Ron?
-Just communicate.
- 罗恩在哪儿?-交流一下。
-(BARN EY GRU NTS)
-Ow! Hey!
噢！嘿！我
I've got a friend, Dad!
有个朋友，爸爸！
The one that saved my life, remember?
那个救了我一命的人，记得吗
-Where is he?
-BOTH: Uh...
？他在哪里？呃..。
Hi. I'm Marc Wydell from Bubble.
你好，我是 Bubble 的马克 · 威德尔。
Where is Ron? If you crushed him...
罗恩在哪里? 如果你压扁了他..。
No, of course not.
Barney, I invented B-Bots.
不，当然不是，巴尼，我发明了 b 型机器人。
They're my dream.
Connection and friendship.
他们是我的梦想，联系和友谊。
But it's not working.
但是没有用。
Except you and Ron. I fixed him.
除了你和 Ron 我治好了他。
-I wanna understand.
-What's up, Barney?
- 我想知道-怎么了，
Ron! You're okay!
巴尼? 荣恩!
-(DINGING)
-What's that?
你没事!-怎么了?
The new number one
on the high-five charts.
击掌排行榜的新冠军。
I now know all 100.
现在我知道了所有的100个。
-Are you okay?
-Doing great, buddy!
- 你还好吗?-很好伙计
Let's go home and check out
your awesome rock collection.
! 我们回家看看你收藏的石头吧。
No. You like electricity.
不，你喜欢电。
I do if you do.
如果你喜欢我就喜欢。
Wait. This isn't Ron.
What did you do to him?
- 等等这不是 Ron 你对他做了
His code was unstable.
什么-他的代码不稳定。
So I re-installed the algorithm...
所以我重新安装了算法..。
He fixed me. Selfie?
他把我修好了。自拍?
(DONKA GROANS)
(唐卡呻吟)-老
-Old women. Not trending.
-Bah.
女人。没上流行趋势。-呸。
RON: Widowed dads, downer!
罗恩: 丧偶的父亲，
-Hey.
-RON: Enhance and post!
令人沮丧的家伙!-嘿。-罗恩: 放大
Un-fix him. It's not him!
照片! 解除治疗。不是他!
N... No. It... It's okay.
不... 不... 没关系。
I backed up Ron to the cloud.
我把罗恩备份到云端。
I'll just log in and I'll find
the old... Huh?
我只要登陆，就能找到以前的... 啊? 他们不能把
They can't lock me out.
I'm the CEO of Bubble.
我锁在外面。我是 Bubble 的 CEO。
ANDREW:
As the new CEO of Bubble,
安德鲁: 作为 Bubble 的新任 CEO,
it’s my sad duty to announce
我很遗憾地宣布，股东
that the shareholders
ha ve wise/y agreed
们已经明智地同意解雇马
to ﬁre Marc Wydell.
克 · 威德尔。
-(FAN FARE PLAYS)
-Andrew! Andrew! Andrew!
- 安德鲁! 安德鲁! 安德鲁
-What?
-BARNEY: Argh.
!-什么。
Barney!
巴尼，
He's in the cloud.
That's what you said, right?
他在云端，你是
-MARC: WeII...
-So take me there.
这么说的，对吧。
-I'm sorry?
-You heard my son.
- 你说什么?-你听到我儿子说的了。
He needs to get to the cloud thing.
他需要搞清楚云计算的事。
And I'm going with him! Uh...
我要和他一起去。
Barney, the cloud
is in a concrete fortress
巴尼，云彩在水泥堡垒里，在泡
half a mile below Bubble.
泡下面半英里处。
There are two million servers
with a zettabyte of data.
有200万台服务器的数据为 zettabyte。
How would you find Ron?
你怎么找到罗恩？
He's my friend.
他是我的朋友。
So take me there and get me in!
那么带我去那里，带我进去！瑞奇: 耶！
RICH: Yeah! Go get
去抓那个变态
-that psycho robot, dude!
-SAVANNAH: Go! Go, Barney!
机器人，伙计！快走！加油，
Okay, Bubble booble.
Let's go get Ron.
巴尼！好吧，泡泡咪。我们去找罗恩。
(MARC CHUCKLES)
(MARC 咯咯笑)
MARC: Okay To get Barney
down into the cloud,
马克: 好吧，把巴尼放进云端,
we ’l/ have to break in past security
我们必须突破过去的安全
and get ﬁght to the heart of Bubble HO.
防线，直捣 HO 泡泡的心脏。
Tomorrow afternoon, all the workers
明天下午，所有的工人
will be watching Andrew
in the launchitorium.
都会在洗衣店看着安德鲁。
That’s our chance.
这是我们的机会。
FEMALE VOICE: All staff
to the launchitorium.
所有工作人员到洗衣店。
All staff to the launchitorium.
AN N O U N C E R: Please welcome
your new OE O, Andrew/
让我们欢迎你们的新成员，安德鲁/(安
(ANDREW WHOOPING)
德鲁呼平)是的，是的，
Yes, yes, yes!
是的，是的！喔-呼
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
-呼-呼！太
Yes! Ha-ha! Love it! (ECHOES)
好了！哈哈！爱死了！我不
(GROANS)
知道你在说什么
-Hi.
-RECEPTIONIST: Hi there!
- 你好-你好! B
How can Bubble help you?.
ubble 能帮你什么忙吗。
-Cleaner!
-Uh, ma'am, you can'tjust...
- 清洁工!-女士你不能就这样..。
-GRAHAM: Sir?
-Ma'am?
- 先生?-女
GRAHAM: Yeah. Can you
take a look at this, please?
士?-是的，你能看看这个吗
Itjust keeps crashing on me.
? 它总是砸在我身上。
And there's a smell of burning
when I hit the space bar.
当我按空格键的时候，有一股烧焦的味道。
Sir, this isn't a Bubble Store.
This is HQ.
先生，这里不是泡泡店，这里是总部。
-(METAL DETECTOR BUZZES)
-DONKA: Oh. Uh...
哦，呃..。
Oh! I just put Bubble in my GPS.
哦! 我刚把 Bubble 放进我的 GPS 里了。
(CHUCKLES) I wondered why
it was a 19-hour drive.
我想知道为什么要开19个小时的车。
Can you look at it anyway?
你能看看吗?
(GRUNTS)
唐卡: 哦
DONKA: Oh, silly me.
(CHUCKLES)
，我真傻。再来一次，
Again, please.
拜托。
(BUZZING)
哦!
Oh! Ooh.
哦。
-Hang... Might be... Ooh.
-(METAL RATTLING)
- 吊... 可能... 哦-(金属
(CHUCKLES SHEEPISHLY)
碰撞声)(怯怯地笑)
(BUZZING)
搜身?
Pat down? (CHUCKLES)
员工
So, workers, colleagues,
shareholders.
同事股东们。
Hi, shareholders. Love ya.
嗨，股东们，爱你们。
Bubble's had a few
minor problems lately, right?
泡沫最近有一些小问题，对吗？
Oof! Yeah.
But here's the good news.
是的，但是有个好消息。
There's nothing wrong
with our B-Bots. It's kids.
我们的 b 型机器人没什么问题只是小孩子。
Kids are the problem.
孩子才是问题所在。
You give a child
an hour of screen time,
你给孩子一个小时的屏幕时间,
you get peace and quiet.
你会得到安宁。
You have his friends around,
all hell breaks loose!
你有他的朋友在身边，一切都乱套了!
Am I right, kids?
我说的对吗，
Stick to your screens.
孩子们? 盯紧你们的屏幕。
Today, your best friend
out of the box becomes...
今天，你最好的朋友从盒子里出来变成了..。
The only friend you ’ll ever need/
你唯一需要的朋友/接待员:
RECEPTIONIST: Just/0g in, sir.
请进，先生。
Okay.
好吧。
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
(电力爆裂声)
-(POWER SHUTS DOWN)
-ANDREW: Huh?
安德鲁: 嗯?
See? That's what it did
at my house.
看到了吗? 它在我家就是这样的。
-(GASPS)
-(ALARM BEEPING)
一切
All good.
正常。
What happened?
发生了什么事?
RECEPTIONIST: (GRUNTS)
Come on!
(咕噜声))来吧!
(UPBEAT SPY MUSIC PLAYING)
(欢快的间谍音乐播放)
Okay. Everybody out.
好了，大家都出去。
This goats smells.
这只山羊很臭。
MARC: Okay. This way.
好的，这边走。
Server room.
Fingerprint recognition.
服务器机房，指纹识别。
-(DONKA GRUNTING)
-Uh...
- (DONKA 咕哝)-呃..。
I fix it.
我修好了。
(GOAT EXCLAIMS)
灯，洒水器，
MARC: Lights, sprinklers,
air-con, security doors.
空调，安全门。
Eat it all, Martina!
吃光它，玛蒂娜! (咩咩
(BLEATS)
声)-(电源关闭
-(POWER SHUTS DOWN)
-ANDREW: What? Uh...
)-安德鲁: 什么? 呃... ..。
(YELPS)
搞什么
What the. . .? (GRUNTS)
...
-BARNEY: Okay.
-You guys go that way.
- 好的-你们走那边。
(CHUCKLES)
Good to see you, buddy.
很高兴见到你，伙计。
What is going on?
- 怎么回事?-
Uh, there's a guy in reception.
呃接待处有个人。
-What?
-It's his laptop.
- 什么?-是他的笔记本电脑。
“Pudowski Novelty Exports"?
Pudowski! That kid!
“ Pudowski 猎奇出口公司”? Pudowski! 那个孩子!
Uh, Andrew. He's in the building.
呃 Andrew 他在楼里。
What?
- 什么?-嘿
GUARD: Hey, yeah.
I think he went down that way.
，是的，我想他从那边下去了。
Down here!
在这里!-啊
-Huh?
-They were right here.
?-他们就在这里。
That is weird.
这太奇怪了。
Okay.
好吧。
Barney, slide along
to the central shaft.
巴尼，滑到中间的竖井去。
The data cab/es inside
lead to down to the cloud.
里面的数据室通向云端。
We ’l/ co ver security and, uh, stuff
我们会处理安全问题的-
-Good luck, Momscke.
-Okay.
祝你好运，妈妈-好的。
(BARNEY WHIMPERING)
好吧
Okay.
。
Of course
they're in the corridors.
当然在走廊里。
-They didn't just vanish!
-(ALARM BEEPING)
- 他们不会就这么消失了
(GASPS)
!-(警报声)
Just go down here.
从这儿下去。
(GASPS)
哇
Whoa.
。
Okay.
好吧。
(GRUNTS)
(咕哝
(GASPS)
)(喘气)
(喘气)
He never mentioned that.
他从没提起过。
What are you doing?
你在干
Uh...
什么。
I... You have problem
with women in workplace?
我。.你对职场女性有意见吗？我从没这么
-I never said that.
-You want to squeeze my knee?
说过。你想捏我的膝盖吗
-What?
-(GOAT BLEATS)
？什么？安德鲁，
Andrew, we found this goat
in the electrics.
我们在电线里发现了这只山羊。
Who are you people?
An improv troupe?
你们是什么人? 一个即兴表演
-(MUFFLED THUD)
-(GASPS)
剧团?-(低沉
(YELPS, SCREAMS)
的声音)-(喘气)(
(YELLING)
尖叫声)(叫喊声)
(GASPS)
(喘气)
(CONTINUES YELLING)
(继续大叫)
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)
我松了
(GRUNTS)
一口气
(GASPING IN AWE)
(敬畏地喘气)
BARN EY: Ron!
巴尼: 罗恩！
Ron!
罗恩！
Where is your snotty little brat?
你那个自大的小鬼在哪里?
He's looking for his friend.
他在找他的朋友。
Friend? (CHUCKLES) Friend?
朋友? 朋友? 嘿，
Hey, are you my friend?
你是我朋
(GRUNTS)
友吗
Sure, Andrew.
当然，安德鲁。
They're just code. A trick.
它们只是代码，一个骗局。
What?
- 什么?-
Data-harvesting units controlled by us.
我们控制的数据收集单位。
Designed to give kids
a consumer experience
旨在为孩子提供消费者体验，特别
featuring products and services
tailored to their browsing profile.
是根据他们的浏览资料量身定制的产品和服务。
The B-Bots know everything about them.
B 型机器人对他们了如指掌。
So we can sell them stuff.
这样我们就可以卖东西给他们。
You're spying on kids?
- 你在监视孩子
I hate kids.
?-我讨厌孩子。
Uh, Andrew. There's someone
inside the cloud.
安德鲁，云里面有人。
What? It's him, isn't it?
什么? 是他，不是吗?-关掉云端。
-Power down the cloud.
-GRAHAM: No!
-格雷厄姆: 不
-DONKA: No.
-And send in security.
!-唐卡: 不。-派保安来。
Ron!
罗恩！
Are you even here?
你到底在不在？
(BARN EY PANTING)
(巴尼喘气)
Oh, no. Where are you?
Barney Pudowski.
- 哦不你在哪儿?-Barney Pudowski。
-(SYSTEM BUZZES)
-Um, seventh grade.
- 嗯，七年级。
(BUZZES)
-(SIGHS)
不是这
Nonsuch Middle School.
样的中学。
(CHIMING)
(钟声)
Uh... What is this?
- 这是什
FEMALE VOICE: Powering down.
么?-关闭电源。
-What's happening?
-System at 70%.
- 怎么回事?-系统70% 。
-No. No, no, no.
-5%.
- 不不不-5% 。
(GASPING)
(喘气)
(VOICE QUIVERING)
Ron, I'll never find you.
罗恩，我再也找不到你了。
And you'll never find me.
你永远也找不到我。
Find me.
找到我。
Find me!
找到
(SHUDDERS)
我
Please.
求你了。
(SIGHS)
(叹气)
(SOFT BUZZING)
(轻微的嗡嗡声)
(SOFT UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING)
(轻音乐响起)
(GASPS)
罗恩，
Ron, I'm coming!
(GRUNTING)
我来了
(CHIMES)
(钟声)
Ron!
罗恩!
Come on, come on!
快点，快点！
Yes! I'm in.
太好了! 我加入。
Barney! (CHUCKLES) He made it.
巴尼! 他成功了。
I found you!
I did it! I found you!
我找到你了! 我找到你了! 我找
Uh, desk, desk.
到你了! 桌子，桌子。
Oh! (CHUCKLES) Okay. Uh...
哦! 好吧。
Here we go.
开始了。
(GASPS)
(喘气)
-(CHUCKLES)
-Hi, Absalom?
- 嗨，押沙龙?
Ron, it's you!
罗恩，是你！
Now I know
what's wrong with him.
现在我知道他怎么了。
Ron never had my algorithm.
罗恩从来没有我的算法。
Whoa!
哇! 这就是
That's his code?
他的代码? 真
It's beautiful. Like...
漂亮，就像..。
Alive.
还活着。
-(GASPS)
-(SIREN BLARING)
他们把
-(BOTH LAUGHING)
-(SINGING) Dikky, dikky, dakka
你变成了
Hey, Ron. They turned you
into electricity...
电流。
Dikky, dikky, dakka
Dikky，Dikky，dakka Di
-...and then put you inside a rock.
-Electricity is best.
kky，Dikky，dakka-... 然后把你放进一块石头里。-电是最好的。
BOTH: You are so annoying!
BARNEY: Whoa, whoa...
- 你真烦人!-哇，哇..。
Please slap my hand
to show we are bonding.
请拍拍我的手，表示我们是一体的。
-(LAUGHS)
-I am within six feet.
我在六英尺之内。
Okay. Then just stay that way,
all right?
好吧，那就保持这样，好吗
'Cause we gotta get out
of here! Come on, Ron.
? 因为我们得离开这里! 快点，罗恩。
Ron?
罗恩？
罗恩? 罗恩: 不，
RON: Not, not your friends.
不是你的朋友。
Iknow. I...
我知道我..。
They are not having fun.
他们没有乐趣。
(SAD MUSIC PLAYING)
(悲伤的音乐播放)
(CAMERA CLICKS)
(照相机点击声)
It's weird.
太奇怪了。
I used to think
that I was the lonely one.
我曾经认为我是孤独的一个。
They need to upgrade to a Ron.
(CHUCKLES)
他们需要升级到荣恩。
-(DINGS)
-I am for making friends.
(笑)-(叮)-我是为了交朋友。
(SNORTS) What?
You mean, for real?
什么? 你是说，真的? 呃，升级他们，
Uh, upgrade them
so they'd all be like you?
让他们都像你一样? 请帮我连
Please connect me to the Bubble network.
接 Bubble 网络。
Two hundred and twenty-five
million Rons out there!
两亿两千五百万个罗恩!-请帮我接通。
-RON: Please connect me.
-(CHUCKLES)
-(笑声)这太疯狂
It would be insane!
I mean, amazing, but...
了! 我的意思是，太神奇了，但是..。
RON: It will be fun.
罗恩: 会很有趣的。
Huh.
哈。
We're right here.
In the middle of the network.
我们就在这里，在网络的中间。
Maybe we could really do this.
也许我们真的可以这么做。
It's our one chance. Now or never.
这是我们唯一的机会，机不可失。
GUARD 1: Systems are down.
GUARD 2: It won't open!
- 系统瘫痪了-打不开！
Uh... Come on, Barney.
What are they doing?
拜托，巴尼，他们在干嘛？
"Upgrade all B-Bots to be like Ron."
“把所有的 b 级机器人升级成罗恩那样。”
(GASPS) Ron's code! Of course.
His code is the fix to mine!
罗恩的密码! 当然，他的密码就是我的密码！
I can help them.
我可以帮助他们。
BARNEY: Marc? He's helping us.
This is how we do it.
马克? 他在帮我们，我们就是这么做的。
-Yes!
-GUARD: Come on, kid, open up!
- 是的!-快点，孩子，
Okay, what do I do?
开门! 好的，
Um, reboot... Wait!
我该怎么做? 嗯，重新启动...
Please connect me
to the Bubble network.
等等! 请帮我连接气泡网络。
Oh! Finally, buddy.
哦! 终于来了，伙计。
Okay. Hold on tight, guys.
You're all getting a Ron!
好了，抓紧了，伙计们。你们都会得到一个荣恩
(STATIC CRACKLING)
! (静态噼啪声)
Ron. Wait,
where are you going?
- 荣恩，等等，你要
Into the network.
去哪里?-进入网络。
No. No way.
不不可能。
You just copy your code
and send that.
你只需要复制你的代码并发送它。
The settings
have not been uploaded.
设置尚未上载。
No, no, no.
His code is fragmenting.
不不不他的代码碎片化了。
He'll disappear! No!
他会消失的! 不!-(
-(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
-(MUFFLED SHOUTING)
敲门)-(低沉的喊叫
(SIGHS)
)(叹气)
We'll just have to go. Forget it.
我们得走了算了。
Come on.
I'm not leaving you behind.
拜托，我不会丢下你的。
Barney.
巴尼。
I am for making friends.
我喜欢交朋友。
BARN EY: What?
巴尼: 什么？
No. You're coming with me.
不，你得跟我走。
How to be a friend.
如何成为朋友。
You taught me.
是你教我的。
(KNOCKI NG CONTI N U ES)
(音乐)(
(MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING)
忧郁音乐)
No. Stay with me. Remember?
不，别离开我，记得吗？
Stay friends.
保持朋友关系。
We can fix it.
我们可以修好它。
You and me.
你和我。
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
现在或
(BREATH ES SHAKILY)
者永远。
Now or never.
(GASPS SHARPLY)
(急喘)(
(SOBS)
哭泣)(忧郁的
(MELANCHOLY MUSIC CONTINUES)
音乐继续)我想我们
I guess we'll...
将..。
(SNIFFLES) we'll swap them all
for a good one.
我们会把它们全部换成一个好的。
The best one.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
最好的一个
Go, Ron. You don't have
to stay within six feet.
快走，罗恩，你不必待在六英尺以内。
Go. Be everywhere.
去吧，去任何地方。
Adio's, Absalom.
再见，押沙龙。
(CHUCKLES)
(笑声)
Arrivederci Ron Bintscatsco.
再会(Ron Bintscatsco)。
(STATIC CRACKLING)
(静态噼啪声)(噼
(CRACKLING STOPS)
啪声停止)
(SIGHS)
(叹气)
(GASPS)
(喘气
(SYSTEM CHIMES, POWERING UP)
)(系统钟声，
(STATIC CRACKLING)
供电)(静
(CHUCKLES)
态噼啪
(LAUGHING)
声)(笑)
(GASPS)
(喘气)
(GASPS IN AWE)
(惊叹))
(GASPS)
(喘气)
(LAUGHING)
- 拜托，
-Come on. What is that?
-What's happening?
那是什么?-
(LAUGHING)
怎么回事
BARN EY: Whoo-hoo!
巴尼: 呜呼！
(GRUNTS)
(咕噜声)
BARN EY: Hi.
巴尼: 嗨。
I, uh, took a wrong turn.
我转错弯了。
Oh. Uh...
哦呃..。
Right.
对。
This way, please.
请这边走。
(STATIC CRACKLING)
(静态噼啪声)
We got him.
我们抓到他了。
Finally. Job done.
终于任务完成了。
(STATIC CRACKLING)
呃，
JOSH: Uh, the cameras.
摄像机。
Barney! Hey! There he is!
巴尼，他来了，
Oh, Barney!
快走
Move it along.
Everybody outta here.
，大家都出去。
Did you...?
你有没有... ?
I'm gonna tell you everything, Dad.
我会把一切都告诉你的爸爸。
On the way home.
在回家的路上。
Okay. Great.
好的很好。
(PANTING)
呜呼!
Whoo-hoo! Whoo-hoo! Etcetera.
呜呼! 等等。
Sorry. Just, um... Uh...
抱歉只是..。
Where were we?
我们说到哪了？
A trick/ Data harvesting units
controlled by us.
一个由我们控制的技巧/数据收集单位。
So we can sell them stuff lhate kids/
所以我们可以卖给他们我讨厌小孩的东西
(GROANS AWKWARDLY)
(尴尬地呻吟)
You know, I've loved my time
as Bubble CEO,
我很喜欢 Bubble 的 CEO 生涯,
and I wanna thank you all
for your support
感谢大家在过去
over the last 32 historic hours.
32个小时里的支持。
But I need to go now
to spend more time with my...
但我现在得走了多花点时间陪陪我的..。
contacts.
接触。
So, please welcome back
所以，让我们欢迎回来-马克
-Marc Wydell.
-(AUDIENCE GASPS)
· 怀德尔。-(观众喘
-(ANDREW WHIMPERING)
-(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
气)-(安德鲁呜咽)-(
AUDIENCE: (CHANTING)
Marc! Marc! Marc!
观众欢呼))马克! 马克! 马
(CHUCKLING)
克! (笑声)
Welcome to the future of friendship.
欢迎来到友谊的未来。
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
(欢呼继续)
(PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING)
(愉快的音乐播
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
放)(学校铃声)
(STATIC CRACKLING)
(静态噼啪声)
STUDENT 1: See you later.
STUDENT 2: Here we go again.
学生1: 再见。学生2: 又来了。
STUDENT 3:
It's gonna get weird.
学生3: 这会变得很奇怪。
BOT 1: That way is good.
BOT 2: This way is good.
机器人1: 这样很好。机器人2: 这样很好。
(BOT GIGGLES)
嘿! 不是说好
Hey! What happened to
staying within six feet?
呆在6英尺以内的吗? 伙计们
Guys, where's my troll bot?
Wait...
，我的喷子机器人呢? 等等..。
I get to choose.
我可以选择。
-(UPBEAT POP MUSIC PLAYING)
-(BOT HUMMING)
韩国流行音乐
K-pop? Are you kidding me?
? 开什么玩笑?
Three months it's been
like this. Come back.
三个月都这样了，回来吧。
Come on, dude.
拜托伙计。
BARN EY: So, here lam again.
贝恩: 那么，我又来了。
E/ghteen minutes
of recess fun. (CH UCKLES)
十五分钟的休息娱乐。(查克莱斯)谢谢
Thanks, Ron. You ﬁxed me.
，罗恩。你把我修好了。
And everyone else.
还有其他所有人。
Hey! We don't know them.
嘿! 我们不认识他们。
I get to choose your friends.
And I choose everyone!
我可以选择你的朋友。我选择每个
Friend request. Friend request.
人! 好友请求。好友请求。
-Hey.
-BOT: Friend request.
- 嘿-好友请求。
You've changed the world,
Barney Pudowski.
你改变了世界，巴尼 · 普多斯基。
How cool is that?
多酷啊? BOT 1:
BOT 1: Friend request.
BOT 2: Friend request.
好友请求。 BOT 2: 好友请求。
Notjust me.
不只是我。
Hey! Oh, my gosh!
嘿! 我的天啊!
Aren't you that girl
that got... You know.
你不是那个... 你知道的。
Video not found.
找不到视频。
Oh. My bad.
我的错。
Thanks. (CHUCKLES)
- 谢谢
Come on.
-来吧。
-BOT 1: Hi, Barney!
-Hey!
- 嗨，巴尼!-嗨
-GIRL: My bot does that every time.
-BOT 2: Hey there.
!-我的机器人每次都这样-嗨。
-Hi.
-GIRL: It's so weird.
- 嗨-太奇怪了。
-BOT 3 AND BARNEY: Hi.
-He's, like, king of the bots.
- 你们好-他是机器人之王。
They love Pudowski.
他们喜欢 Pudowski。
Barn, you have got to get back
in that Bubble cloud place.
巴恩，你必须回到那个泡沫云的地方。
(ALL SHUSH)
让这个机器人
And get this bot to stop
making up its own game rules.
停止制定自己的游戏规则。
BOT: Free upgrades for everyone!
BOT: 每个人都可以免费升级！
-How am I ever gonna win?
-(ALL LAUGH)
- 我怎么才能赢呢?-(笑声)
Dude! We gotta tell 'em!
伙计，我们得告诉他们！
You pranked a global
freakin' tech giant, man!
你恶作剧了一个全球性的科技巨头！
Please let me stream
the reveal, bro, please?
请让我把这个展示传过来，兄弟，好吗？
Take it from me, Rich.
Fame is overrated.
相信我，瑞奇，名声被高估了。
(CHUCKLES)
Look what I brought.
看我带了什么来。
-I'll take one.
-One for everyone.
- 我要一个-每人一个。
-Cheers!
-ALL: Cheers!
- 干杯!-干杯!
Barney! Hey! You see?
巴尼! 嘿! 你看到了
I told you my bench would work!
吗? 我告诉过你我
-(CLUCKING)
-Oh!
的长凳会起作用的!-哦
Yeah. It's great.
! 是的。太棒了。
(ALL LAUGH)
你奶奶做的
Mmm. Is all your gran's food this good?
菜都这么好吃吗?
Come... Come over sometime.
Hang out.
有空过来坐坐。
I know you're dying to
see my rock collection.
我知道你很想看看我收藏的石头。
Will she set us on fire again?
她会再次放火烧我们吗?-希望如此
-Hope so.
-That was so fun!
。-那真是太有趣了!
But you're gonna have to talk
to that goat,
但是你得和那只山羊谈谈,
because I do not want
any more of my jewelry
因为我不想再让我的珠宝穿
going through its intestines.
过它的肠子了。
(ALL LAUGHING)
(笑声))(
(PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING)
愉快的音乐播放)
(POP SONG PLAYING)
(流行歌曲播放)(静态噼啪
(STATIC CRACKLING, GLITCHING)
，闪烁) Dikky，
Dikky, dikky, dakka
Dikky，dak
(SYSTEM POWERS DOWN, BLEEPS)
ka (系统电源关闭，BLEEPS
(BEEPING)
)(哔哔声)
(BEEPING INTENSIFIES)
(哔哔声加强)
(UPTEMPO POP SONG PLAYING)
(快节奏流行歌曲播放)
(UPBEAT POP SONG PLAYING)
(欢快的流行歌曲播放)
(ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(电子音乐播放)